Halfway through a kiss,
Miracle Girls
tears dropped out.
Original Work by Nanami Akimoto
(Serialized in "Nakayoshi")
Character Design:
Yoshihisa Sekine
Series Coordinator:
Hirokazu Kobayashi
Because I closed my heart
Filming Director:
Hieao Shirai
Art Director:
Takashi Nakamura
and distanced myself from you.
5 PM in the school yard.
Music:
Michiru Oshima
Filming Director:
Hieoao Shirai
The ball's shadow is growing tall.
Opening Song
"Halfway Through a Kiss, Tears"
("Kiss no Tochu de Namida ga")
by GARDEN
Don't be so quiet.
Ending Song
"There has to be Both of Us"
("Futarijanakya Dame Nano")
By Dio
Whenever we meet in the hallway,
we always quarreled.
Halfway through a kiss,
Producers:
Shinichiro Maeda,
Yuhko Sasagawa
& Ken Yorita
tears dropped out.
Because I opened my heart
Created by
Nihon TV
and we understand each other.
Produced by
Japan Taps & ASATSU
Translation by
Naoki Mizutani
Episode 20
Hurricane in
Maiden's Heart
Working as hard as ever, aren't you?
What do you want, sir?
I'm going over to a newspaper company.
They seem to got interested in my work in ESP and wants to see me.
That's good for you. Hope it works out for you, not like the last time...
Looks like my works are going to be published in very near future.
My project is also approaching completion.
It's bitter and sweet work.
Would you like to give it a try?
One sip and you'll be in dreamy paradise.
Only if you're willing to exchange your life for that though.
In exchange for my life?
Please, don't be reserved.
I'm not reserving myself.
Sensei!
NOOOO!
Too bad for him.
Perfect. Guys, coffee is ready.
Tomomi!
You're late, Noda-kun.
Sorry.
Why didn't you wear that?
That?
That's mean! Remember, you promised.
But.. it's too embarrassing, you know?
How could you? It was my dream..  It's my dream to date.
So it was your dream...
We bought in pair.
But if we run into our friends, they might take it in wrong way.
Something wrong with that?
Nothing at all.
I forgot. I'm hungry.
Let's talk about this later, and why don't we grab something to eat?
What do you say? This's my research essay on twin ESPers.
It's you again.
- This paper would astonish the world.
- Hello?
Excuse me. I've got an unexpected guest.
Wait till you see this! With this paper, your paper will double the sales.
Our local section reporter is itching to hear your story.
I'll show you the way.
Oh, I see.
That's the local section.
I'm very grateful for your help.
Thank you.
You are welcome.
Hey, this's the back door.
Would you try another paper?
What?
Good bye.
See ya tomorrow.
Will you knock it off?
The editor is in a meeting.
Now, will you leave?
This's a big scoop!
My essay!
What? A whirlwind?
Don't go! My history making essay!
Large and powerful Typhoon #3 will head north and hit Honshu by tomorrow evening.
I don't believe this. It's still May.
Oh wow!
What are we?
Something happened with Noda?
Can you tell me what Noda-kun and I are?
What made you say that?
I never really checked how he felt about me.
He's a bit dull, but I'm sure he knows how you feel about him.
I need to be sure about his feeling to me.
Naturally occurring radioactive isotopes are classified into three groups.
"Be" verb plus present particle, that is, "ing" added to the root.
For instance, "Tom is looking out of the window."
Hey!
Sorry.
The mid term is coming up soon.
Pay attention or you'll get a "F" mark again.
You hit me with the corner.
Destroy everything and create something anew.
What's wrong, Matsunaga-san?
What's wrong, Younger Matsunaga?!
Due to the approaching of typhoon, the afternoon classes are canceled.
All students, please go home immediately. I repeat...
How are you feeling?
Better. And you?
I'm fine. But I wonder why both of us collapsed at the same time.
Looks like nobody else heard the noise.
Most likely...
What?
Our telepathy linked, and synced with something.
You heard that sharp sound in ears, right?
And had a shock like electricity ran through my body.
My ears are still ringing.
Me too.
That's one down side of telepathy, I guess.
Who's that?
Oops, noticed me? Bummer, I wanted to surprise you two.
You wanted to peep, right?
Is that all you got to say when I dropped by worried about you?
What worry?
You just wanted to scared us and see if we pass out again.
Tomomi, I gotta pick up something, so go ahead and go home.
Now, the bugger can go home alone.
Stop, Younger Matsunaga.
I heard all your conversation in the medical room.
I'd like to know more about the telepathy.
Date?
I'll be waiting at the same spot as yesterday.
But looks at the weather.
Don't you think date in a typhoon is gonna be fun?
Then, promise me you'll come.
Promise?... Wait, Tomomi!
Why today, not tomorrow?
Hey, stop Tomomi!
Tomomi!
Are you sure?
Sure, if you really want to know, I can show you.
Don't tell me this is a hoax.
But don't you hold me responsible for whatever could happen to you.
Why should I? There's no way!!
Was that you?
I'll leave it up to your imagination.
Will you quit laughing?
I mean, Kageura was scared as hell,
thinking even the thunder was because of me.
He's too funny.
It's not funny at all.
Why did you tell Kageura?
Don't know.
I just suddenly felt like making fun of Kageura.
Large and powerful Typhoon #3 has picked up strength, and...
will land in Honshu by the evening.
That's right.
I felt I should big papers like your's should know.
After all, this is an event of the century.
Don't tell me you're serious about showing ESP to Kageura-sensei.
I am.
I told him I'll show it today.
But imagine what kind of trouble we could be in!
Come on. It'll make us feel easier.
We can't be ordinary high school students anymore!
But Kurashige-sempai and Noda already know.
But they're exception.
Remember we promised to keep it secret to even dad or mom.
How dare they take me so lightly!
Shin-chan, lunch is ready.
Sure.
Enjoy it.
Thank you for food.
Who could do this?
We found a penguin with an arrow piercing its body in Inokashira Park.
Delicious, Rika-chan.
Good. I'm glad I got the ingredients from Papua New Guinea.
Shin-chan, watch your manner.
So, is there anybody in the audiences who experienced strange things like this?
Call us right away.
Our blitz reporter will get to you very quick.
This is it.
I'm tired of hiding.
I just want to tell everything and get it over with.
But...
I'm gonna do it.
At last! The moment I have been waiting for is here!!
The day has finally come for me to be the big name in science world!
Date with Noda?
You got it.
But there's a typhoon.
Why don't you change to another day?
I can't. We already promised.
I get this feeling that I can find out Noda-kun's feeling to me today.
But Tomomi...
I want to get rid of this uncertainty.
You aren't acting like yourself.
Neither you are.
Of all other days, why today?
I wonder if it's OK with her if the sweat shit get all wet.
What's she up to?
Are you certain, we'll get to see the greatest twin ESPer of the century?
Of course. Why else would I call you people?
But why do you have to carry out the experiment in the middle of typhoon?
Can't you see? The strange power within typhoon enhance the strength of ESP.
Be sure to film it properly.
It's going to be the biggest event of the century.
Wait.
I'll teleport you so that you can make it to the date, so will you come with me first?
Why don't you go alone?
Tomomi.
What a pushy girl you are.
Sorry.
End it in three minutes.
Okay.
Younger Matsunaga, glad you kept your promise.
I'm sorry to startle you.
It's hard to see you two in this storm with just lights of the park.
Don't worry about it.
Now can you begin?
In the middle of this storm, it'll begin.
We're just about to see the history in making.
She told me to come and she's late.
What's the...
A tornado?
Tomomi, are you OK?
Hey, Mikage!
Tomomi!
Noda-kun.
Noda-kun, I love you.
Hey, don't embarrass me..
Congrats, Tomomi.
You only had the tornado on the video?! Forget it!
How dare they call me boaster!
Just wait and see.
I won't give up!
Mikage, it feels so good doing this!
Why did we do that?
Don't know.
Morning.
Morning. Thank you about yesterday.
Don't mention it.
I really don't remember about it.
Did I say something when you came to save me?
Nothing I can remember.
I see. Never mind.
Miracle Girls here.
She's lost in hiking.
There're bears around here.
Don't worry. Noda-kun's with you.
What? With him?
Next on Miracle Girls:
"Bearing to South South West"
Why do I have to be lost with Noda?
Whatever we do,
there has to be both of us.
Even if we had a fight,
There has to be both of us.
Ending Song
"There has to be Both of Us"
("Futarijanakya Dame Nano")
By Dio
There are days when kindness is so close
that you can't see it.
Even if we know it better than anyone else.
When we can't say "I'm sorry,"
we send out feelings through the little fingers.
Going over the tears,
we want to be honest to ourselves.
'Cause the sky deserves a rainbow.
Whatever we do,
there has to be both of us.
Two of us
are better than one of us.