Halfway through a kiss,
Miracle Girls
Tears dropped out.
Because I closed my heart
and distanced myself from you.
5 PM in the school yard.
The ball's shadow is growing tall.
Don't be so quiet.
Ending Theme
Whenever we meet in the hallway,
we always quarreled.
Halfway through a kiss,
tears dropped out.
Because I opened my heart
and we understand each other.
Episode 9
Snow  Storm
at the Lodge
Wow, look at the snow!  It's white all over!
Look, Mikage.  It's snow.
Hey!
Morning.
Good morning, Tomomi.
A festival?
They fight against a snowman.
It's supposed to be awesome.
You aren't scary at all.
I'll eat you up!
I'm stuffed.
It's cute.
Now, let's dump our stuff and go skiing.
I wanna hit the slope.
Welcome to my lodge.  I've been expecting you.
What do you think of the lodge my father runs?
Yeah, it's awesome.
I'm starving.
Hold it.  I'm not done with explaining.
You wanna brag, right?
Certainly not.
How my sense is reflected on the construction of the lodge is...
So, you're bragging, aren't you?
I see.  Now the climax of the festival poses a question.
What could this path of the spirit be?
It's not mentioned in the pamphlet at all.
Doesn't matter.
Now I'm getting the picture.  Rika, the snowman does exist after all.  Soon, we'll find one.
That's nice.
I'll get solid proof this time.  I love it.
Our future is promised!
It's getting worse over there.
They're still at it?
I bet she's still blabbing about the door or the wall.
So, I said, I heard you.
Oh no.  You haven't seen the design of the pillar there.
Yes, I saw it.
No, you didn't.  Now look.
Help, Tomomi !
Now what?
Nothing we can do.
Wait.
Forget it.
You didn't hear what I said.
Knock it off.
Wow, a snowman.  Awesome.
Scary.
Really.
I'm not done yet.
Leave me alone!
That's a bad omen.
I... I'm sorry.
Are you OK?
I'm terribly sorry.  They really don't know any manners.
Ah!  Please don't worry.
Yes, I do.
Really, it's alright.
Just in case, can I have your phone number, address, and measurements?
Please, I'm quite OK.
But I insist.
Ms. Emma Easton, there is a phone call for you.
Excuse me.
That's strange...
What?  A rock?
Must be a mark for something.
This could be where the snowman comes.
Let's get closer.
Watch your step, Rika.
It's cute.
Right?  After all, I chose all the interior design.
See this bed cover?
So, she's got something to brag about everywhere.
I envy her.
She's at the Rosebud inn.
There's nothing good over there.
Why?
The snowman is around.
Sounds fun.
She's got nothing to brag about.
There might be a real snowman.
I wonder.
It's true.  There is one.
Really, there is one.
Now, that's awesome.
You don't believe me, do you?
Yes, I do.
No, you don't.
But it'd be fun if there's one.
It's there.
Let's catch him ourselves.
Why don't we go see the festival?
Everything is gone.
Now I see.
What is it, honey?
It's the snowman.
Snowman?
The snowman must have taken everything.
He's trying to stop us because I found a clue.
You got F for math, didn't ya?
What did you get on Japanese?
Hey, don't even think about it !
Oh yeah?!  Here's a powerful one!
No way!  You missed me.  You missed me.
I'm sorry.  You dropped it.
Umm... thank you.
Hey!  Noda!
What's up?
Nothing.
Grandma.
Hello.  Nice to see you again.
Excuse me.
Uh... yes?
Excuse me, is this the way to the lodge?
Uh... no, it's not.
That's weird.  I'd swear it was this way.
You must've taken a wrong road.  You're heading the wrong way.
Let's head back.
Sure.
Thank you for your direction.
You're welcome.
We're heading back to the snowman's cave.  Hang onto me.
Yes, Shin.
I attend Minato International School.
That's in our neighborhood.
Are you interested in traditional Japanese culture and customs?
Yes.  Especially legends and myths are interesting.
Then, do you know about the snowman legend in this region?
I came to find out about that.
There was a man who came to ask about the legend yesterday.
What did he look like?
I think he was a school teacher.
I see.
I don't think it'll go away that soon.
"yuguradoshirutoneriko"
No need to open it.
It'll come in if it wants to.
Oh, Shin.
Rika, hang in there.  I'll save you.
Let's get it over with and have a drink.
Rika.
Yamagishi, you deal with that.  I'll take care of the door.  Let's go, Tomomi.
"yuguradoshirutoneriko"
Let's go.
Get something to hold it.
Let's give it our best shot.
Mikage, what's the use of that?
This?
Gimme a hand with this.
OK.
Danger.
"yuguradoshirutoneriko"
Mikage!
Tomomi.
Mikage, do you hear it?
Yeah.  What is it?
Don't know.
"yuguradoshirutoneriko"
Gotta nail it down from outside.  Can you get Noda?
Emma, can you find a hammer and some nails?
Yes.
Noda.
Rika, we're getting there.  I see the old lady's house.
Yes.
Daijoji, what's wrong?  What is it?
Noda, Yamagishi needs you.
What happened to her?
Don't know.
Stop crying and tell us.
We need some firewood.  Something to keep the fire going.
What's going on, ma'am?
We must keep the fire going.
Ma'am.
Tomomi, there.
Great, hammer.
Got nails.
Good, let's go.
What happened to Daijoji?
Looked like she was scared of something.
Did you see something?
Looked like a person.
What's wrong?
We ran out of firewood.
Firewood is over there.
That ought to do.
Trouble?
What were those bums?
That's no way to treat ladies.
What happened?
Some stranger came in...
What did they do to you?
They just threw us.
What a relief.
What about Mikage?
I don't need your concern.
What?!
Mikage, are you hurt?
Same to you.
Where's Emma?
They're after her.
Forget it.  You two go downstairs.
Knock it off.  Can't you stay still?
But I'm worried.
There's nothing you can do.
You're right, but...
Noda?
I think so.
What's going on?
Hold it !
They're just kids.
Some big kids they were.
Noda.
Yamagashi.
Lady Emma.
Who are you people?
I bet she jumped from here.
I'm surprised she did.
It's us.
Teacher!
We came for skiing and we haven't at all !
What's going to happen in this mountain?
Something big and something wonderful.
Next time on Miracle Girls,
"Avalanche  Warning"
Is an avalanche wonderful?
Original air date Mar 5, 1993.
Whatever we do,
there has to be both of us.
Matsunaga Tomomi ...Fujieda Nariko
Matsunaga Mikage........Nagai Noriko
Even if we had a fight,
there has to be both of us.
Noda Yuhya...........Yamaguchi Kappei
Kurashige Hideaki...Shiozawa Kaneto
Miracle Girls on internet http://www.tcp.com/doi/miracle/miracle.html
There are days when kindness is so close that you can't see it.
Miracle Girls Original Soundtrack Sony Records SRCL 2574
Shinichiroh Kageura...Ken Yamaguchi
Daijohji Rumiko.................Sakuma Rei
Even if we know better than anyone else.
Yamagishi Kouhei.......Nobuh Tobita
Original script by Arctic Animation.
Script updated by Resub Boy.
Additional editing by Miwa.
When we can't say "I'm sorry,"
Subtitled by Studio Hooseki.
www.miwasoft.com/hooseki
we send out feelings through the little fingers.
Going over the tears,
we want to be honest to ourselves.
'Cause the sky deserves a rainbow.
Whatever we do,
there has to be both of us.
Two of us
are better than one of us.