Halfway through a kiss,
Miracle Girls
tears dropped out.
Original Work by Nanami Akimoto
(Serialized in "Nakayoshi")
Character Design:
Yoshihisa Sekine
Series Coordinator:
Hirokazu Kobayashi
Because I closed my heart
Filming Director:
Hieao Shirai
Art Director:
Takashi Nakamura
and distanced myself from you.
5 PM in the school yard.
Music:
Michiru Oshima
Filming Director:
Hieoao Shirai
The ball's shadow is growing tall.
Opening Song
"Halfway Through a Kiss, Tears"
("Kiss no Tochu de Namida ga")
by GARDEN
Don't be so quiet.
Ending Song
"There has to be Both of Us"
("Futarijanakya Dame Nano")
By Dio
Whenever we meet in the hallway,
we always quarreled.
Halfway through a kiss,
Producers:
Shinichiro Maeda,
Yuhko Sasagawa
& Ken Yorita
tears dropped out.
Director:
Takashi Anno
Because I opened my heart
Created by
Nihon TV
and we understand each other.
Produced by
Japan Taps & ASATSU
Translation by
Naoki Mizutani
Episode 18
Unicorn under
Moonlight
P.i.n.e.a.p.p.l.e.
It's only a matter of chance. Anybody can win one out of ten.
Scissors, paper, rock.
Alright! I win again.
They're late. What's holding them?
Scissors, p..
I can't see you!
Yeah, you said your eye sight went down again.
Fine, let's do it with telepathy.
OK, I'll win three in a row this time.
Scissors, paper, ...
I'll phone Tomomi's home.
I'll get going. See ya.
Dammit, I wanna see nude, too.
P.i.n. e.a.p. p.l.e... What about noodle?
Nothing at all.
You're late. What took you so long?
Sorry. I was play with Mikage.
Do scissors paper rock, win with paper, you make steps saying "pineapple."
Most kids stop playing that after elementary school.
But it's pretty fun.
And where's Mikage?
Mikage, Mikage, I'm already at the art museum.
Kurashige-sempai's awesome.
Yeah, he sent in a sketch from England, and that got selected...
in the prefectural high school art contest.
Hey, this way, Noda! There's a nude painting!
Tomomi, where are you?
Over here. Come on. Sempai's sketches are great.
Mikage, there you are. Sempai's drawings are over here.
What do you sense out of this painting, Yamagishi-kun?
I'd say this curvature of bust is quite artistic.
There.
Wonderful, aren't they?
I feel sempai's blending into London.
Like he might have forgotten about us and became Londoner.
No way. Look. This one looks like you.
Sempai...
Mikage, weren't sempai's drawings great?
After all, it's him. How could it be lousy?
A raccoon?
It's a bear!
He's going further away.
He's moving again? To Egypt?
I meant...
We've got Kageura's exam tomorrow!
I'm going to sleep.
Aren't you lucky? You don't have to panic over exam.
You wanted to see me?
How come you came to see me?
Mikage! Mikage!
Mikage, you'll be late again.
Isn't she lucky sleeping sound and happy on the day of chem exam?
I had dream that Kageura-sensei just keep on laughing at me.
The worst nightmare I've ever had.
Dream? Was it a dream?
That's the unicorn's scent.
You may begin. I have gathered assortment of impossible questions bad...
enough to make you see nightmares for a next week or two.
I'll be done with this easy stuff real quick.
Then, let's play together again.
With such a dreamy face, I am bound to win.
Are you finished already?
Yes.
Now, you're twelve minutes faster than my estimate. Was it that easy?
May I leave?
Don't disturb others.
What? Impossible.
Sempai used to watch sea from here.
See? You can see the ocean really well, right?
You know about sempai, don't you?
His picture is in the same art museum as you.
He's the one who drew the pictures of London.
Don't tickle me.
Come on, knock it off.
I couldn't believe it. Even scientist wouldn't be able to get those questions.
At least if he could ask us what's covered in text book.
Who the hell would study about undiscovered elements on the night side of the moon.
How long has she been asleep?
Damn Mikage.
Sempai used to hang around here, didn't he?
London's too far away, isn't it?
If I go abroad, would you remember about me when you stand on the race track?
No way, right? I'm gonna blow the exam anyway.
And with English its just about the same.
And how can you go study abroad?
Say Mikage, wanna have chips?
Mikage
Mikage, where are you going?
Wait!
Take me to London.
Who are you talking to?
Take me to sempai.
Mikage
Mikage! Mikage!
Are you asleep?
Mikage...
There's something here?
It's so pretty. It's like stars forming a river.
The moonlight is the same wherever you are.
The same wherever I am?
Dammit, what does she usually eat?
Tomomi.
You're up? Why were you wandering around in midnight?
You had me worried.
Tomomi.
What?
I was playing with the unicorn. I'll show him to you.
Thus, oxygen react with most of other elements to form an oxide.
And oxides are classified into...
oxides, peroxides and superoxides.
It was heck of a news. Of all people Mikage blew the chem exam.
What happened to her?
She's been acting weird.
Is she sick?
She muttered something about unicorn.
There. Unicorn: one of most popular imaginary beast.
It supposedly weave human dreams.
Weave dream?
So, it draws people into dream word.
So you came again.
It is a real unicorn...
Tomomi. Tomomi, you can see him too?
I'm glad!
I was thinking of taking you to a ride with him even if I have to drag you out of bed.
Mikage.
Sure, let's fly with him.
Take us to London!
Let's call Noda-kun over, too.
Sure.
Good!
Scissors, paper, rock.
I win.
Mikage, you better win or we'll leave you there.
Scissors, paper, rock.
So, Mikage lose again.
Wait! Don't leave me here!
Mikage, here we go. Scissors, paper, rock.
Alright, Mikage-kun win!
Mikage, come over!
With grand special unicorn, I want to see sempai real badly.
Now you caught up with us.
Mikage.
One more time.
Scissors, paper, rock.
Let's go.
The moonlight is the same wherever you are.
London, or Yokohama, it's all the same.
Nothing will change, I'm sure.
Yeah.
Saw dream about sempai?
Me too. All of us were playing scissors, paper, rock.
Was the moon pretty?
It was.
Miracle Girls here.
Oh god. A dinosaur appeared!
A dinosaur?
It popped out of a fossil suddenly.
Could that be a ghost of a dinosaur?
Next on Miracle Girls:
"Voice Calling into Fog"
It must be looking for others.
Whatever we do,
there has to be both of us.
Even if we had a fight,
There has to be both of us.
Ending Song
"There has to be Both of Us"
("Futarijanakya Dame Nano")
By Dio
There are days when kindness is so close
that you can't see it.
Even if we know it better than anyone else.
When we can't say "I'm sorry,"
we send out feelings through the little fingers.
Going over the tears,
we want to be honest to ourselves.
'Cause the sky deserves a rainbow.
Whatever we do,
there has to be both of us.
Two of us
are better than one of us.