Halfway through a kiss,
Kissu no tochu de namida ga
Miracle Girls
tears dropped out.
Koborete shimau
Original Work by Nanami Akimoto
(Serialized in "Nakayoshi")
Character Design:
Yoshihisa Sekine
Series Coordinator:
Hirokazu Kobayashi
Because I closed my heart
Kokoro tozashite anata o
Filming Director:
Hieao Shirai
Art Director:
Takashi Nakamura
and distanced myself from you.
Touzakaete itakara
5 PM in the school yard.
PM5/go ji no koutei
Music:
Michiru Oshima
Filming Director:
Hieoao Shirai
The ball's shadow is growing tall.
Ball no kage mo nagai
Opening Song
"Halfway Through a Kiss, Tears"
("Kiss no Tochu de Namida ga")
by GARDEN
Don't be so quiet.
Sonna mukuchi de inaide
Ending Song
"There has to be Both of Us"
("Futarijanakya Dame Nano")
By Dio
Whenever we meet in the hallway,
Rouka de au tabi
we always quarreled.
Kenka shiteta noni
Halfway through a kiss,
Kiss no tochu de namida ga
Producers:
Shinichiro Maeda,
Yuhko Sasagawa
& Ken Yorita
tears dropped out.
Koborete shimau
Because I opened my heart
Kokoro hiraite subete ga
Created by
Nihon TV
and we understand each other.
Tsuji aeta kara
Produced by
Japan Taps & ASATSU
Tomomi...
Hurry up, hurry up! What are you doing?
I know, I'm coming now.
We have enough time, so don't be in a hurry.
I don't mean that. See?
Eh?
Oh, it was sunny earlier.
It's my first time wearing this dress.
I don't want it to get dirty before we arrive at the hospital.
OK I see. Lets go!
Tomomi...
It's just a drizzle. If we wait for a while, it's going to stop.
It's Tomomi's fault because you were too slow.
Ok ok.
My my, what ill mannered girls.
Miracle Girls #25
Mysterious weather
You two, I feel guilty over your wasting the holiday.
No way. We really don't care about that. Right Tomomi?
Of course.
When I came back I wanted to go travel with everybody,
but I can't because of my leg.
Senpai.
If you got well we could go as many times as we want.
But could you apologize to Noda?
I'm sorry I got in your way on such a wonderful day for a date.
Date?
Well... I'll go get some hot water.
How come you didn't tell me that?
Don't worry about it.
Oh my gosh.
I'm so sorry. Are you OK?
I'm OK, I'm pretty tough.
But your flowers...
What?
Are you OK? Be careful, it's dangerous if you bump into someone on crutches, right?
Yes!
And when you do secret talking, first all of you check around, and then do it.
Secret talking? She means our telepathy?
Huh?
Why are you depressed? You can come here again after school.
I know, but I think Kurashige senpai might feel down.
That's right.
I'm frustrated because I can't do anything for him.
Oh come on, don't be so gloomy.
It doesn't suit you.
Okay, let's go home in order to not get the dress wet.
Alright.
Oh oh, it looks like rain again.
If you hurry you won't be wet.
The bus...
See, you better run to catch it!
Yes!
Wait Tomomi!
We're getting on, wait!
Come on...
Meanie.
Tomomi, why'd you run?
Because that woman...
Eh, she's gone.
Mikage, hey Mikage. Haven't you finished yet?
You see I told Kagera I'd visit for sure...
...and you won't be in on time.
That's why I said wait a minute.
Matsunaga.
Who could it be that you were talking to?
There's only me and you,
or might you have been talking telepathically?
No way.
I couldn't make it because of you.
Matsunaga, if you could make it, what do you intend it to be?
A.. terrific one..
Tomomi.
I'm sorry, let's go.
Why don't you visit him tomorrow?
No, I promised him I'd visit everyday.
But the visiting hours will be finished soon.
That's why I asked you to wait here for me.
Just a moment...
Well, is anybody around?
It looks alright, let's go.
You two.
Do you know what you're stepping on?
Eh, stepping on?
Well what are you doing just standing there then?
Oh no!
Get out of the flower bed.
Have you been watching us?
You're forgetting to say something, aren't you.
We're sorry.
That's right, don't forget that.
Well today's visiting hours are finished so go home with care and fix the flower bed.
You got it? How about the answer?
Yes.
Good.
What is that about?
Did she see our teleportation?
No way. If she did, she'd be very surprised.
By the way... Do we have to give up even though we came to the hospital?
But...
Please.
Quiet!
And now he's having an X-ray, so it's gonna take more time.
Anyway, it's impossible for today.
Maybe you'll have better luck tomorrow.
Try not to catch a cold.
Who is that apron twit?
Yeah there's something strange about her.
We must've done something nasty to warrant a grudge like that.
Or rather, she seems to know about us.
Come on.
You see, whenever we use telepathy, she's around.
No way, you think too much.
The timing is always exact.
That's true.
Whenever we meet her, it would rain afterwards.
That's also true.
That's it, monster rainy woman. Next time I see her, she's going down!
Mikage, are you thinking seriously?
Of course.
Well, is she here?
What, do you think she'll sneak up on us again?
I'm not about to take such an unscientific attitude. It won't be raining today.
That's right.
Are you Ok?
May I help you?
Oh really?
You really saved me.
Is this gonna be all?
Thanks again, you're such a lifesavers.
You feel fresh after working hard, right?
No way.
The sun in between showers is especially beautiful.
Maybe it's the same as after a good sweat no crying.
Um, you are...
Then, if you've hung it all to dry, we're done here.
Come on hurry up, or you'll be late for visiting.
Great, it didn't get dirty.
Will you bring this one upstairs?
Hmm, you think so...
Oh sorry, I had my sheet blown off by a strong wind.
Could you bring this one up also?
What the heck is this!?
No way.
Not for sale
Not for rent
That's a problem.
That parrot is the mascot for children and seniors who are patients.
If they knew he was gone, they'd be upset.
What're we going to do?
It can't be helped. Why don't you apologize with some excuse?
Otherwise you guys can't come back here.
Wait a minute.
How come we can't come back here because of such a small problem?
Such a small problem?
Yes, it is.
All right. It might be a small problem for you because you can go anywhere as you like.
But these patients cannot go out to find the parrot or buy another bird.
I seem to remember your friend falling into this category. Now he can't go out as he likes, right?
When I came back I wanted to go travel with everybody,
but I can't because of my leg.
Mikage, let's go apologize.
I'm gonna go find the parrot. That woman can't go laying guilt trips on me.
Mikage.
It's gonna be wonderful if you can find it.
Let's do it, but without your magic.
Of course you'll do it for the patients.
That's a promise.
She knows about us as I expected.
So why is she so nasty to us?
Is that nasty?
What do you mean, I thought you were on my side?
Don't take it out on me. This thing happened because you dropped the sheet.
Alright, just watch it rain woman. Don't underestimate Mikage!
Then, how can we find it?
Excuse me, did you see a parrot like this big?
I'm afraid not.
Did you see a green parrot around here?
Nope, I didn't see it.
Hey kids, did you see a parrot like this big anywhere?
Where did that parrot go?
Mikage!
Mikage, I found a person who saw the parrot.
Really?
They said they saw a parrot in the forest over by the park.
Tomomi. Tomomi stop... I can't run anymore.
Pull yourself together. We've gotta find the parrot in a hurry or it's gonna be dark.
but...
I get it, wait here while I go explore a bit more.
What a bad day. I'll miss the visiting hours again.
I can't meet senpai today either.
If we find it you can meet him as many times as you like.
How come we have to do such a stupid thing?
There!
Tomomi
But, we promised her we won't use that.
We don't have any choice.
Don't cheat.
What are you...
We promised without magic. Or can't you do it normally?
How...
Don't take the easy way, at least you can run cheerfully.
Don't forget all you can do as a normal girl.
As a normal girl?
It flied this way right?
Tomomi just wait. Stop!
She's a rain woman after all.
But I'm a little concerned about it.
Exactly, she's not nice at all.
No, I'm referring to when she said to not forget all we can do as normal girls.
Normal?
That woman always shows up whenever we use telepathy.
If you bump into someone on crutches or the like, it's gonna be dangerous right?
And when you do secret talking, don't forget to check first.
Do you two know what you're stepping on?
Oh I'm sorry. I had my sheet blown off by a strong wind.
Well that shows if we didn't use telepathy or teleportation
we wouldn't bump into people or step on flowers.
What do we do?
We can't catch him in this situation.
Mikage!
Cat!!
That parrot doesn't notice.
No it doesn't open.
Run away!
Hurry up! Run away!
You're in a dangerous situation.
Tomomi!
To the balcony!
Too bad kitty.
We made it.
But we used magic.
Where is she?
That person.
Right, that rain woman might be watching us and then show up to say something.
But that's all right because we could help the parrot.
I know but I feel frustrated because we had to use power to find a parrot.
Mikage!
Who are you?
You two found the parrot with magic.
You knew that, after all.
Your friend and any patient can't go running out,
so spare a thought about those people if you get wet.
You mean we had better not use magic?
I didn't say that, because if you didn't have that power, this parrot wouldn't have been saved, right?
It's no problem provided you only use your power for the proper occasions.
Well then.
That's...
I have a new bridge so it's time to go to a new town.
Wait! Who are you?
Rain woman, right?
That's...
She disappeared.
Over there!
No way.
See you, Miracle girls.
Parrot? In the hospital? I don't think so...
Do they have it or do you know a nurse who has a big apron?
Or somebody's attendant?
Well, I've never heard that before, and this hospital is all nursing so there's no attendants.
You might have a misunderstanding.
Then, that person...
What are you talking about?
Never mind.
It's alright, it must be our mistake.
Yeah, that's it.
Wow senpai isn't that great?
Have a look.
Finally the rain has passed.
So it has, hasn't it?
Who was that woman?
Mikage! I was scouted for volleyball!
That's great Tomomi, I'm going to support you all the way!
Are you sure, if I accept that I'll transfer to a different school.
Next on Miracle Girls,
"I'll transfer to a different school!"
Ending Song
"There has to be Both of Us"
("Futarijanakya Dame Nano")
By Dio
Whatever we do,
there has to be both of us.
Even if we had a fight,
There has to be both of us.
There are days when kindness is so close
that you can't see it.
Even if we know it better than anyone else.
When we can't say "I'm sorry,"
we send out feelings through the little fingers.
Going over the tears,
we want to be honest to ourselves.
'Cause the sky deserves a rainbow.
Whatever we do,
there has to be both of us.
Two of us
are better than one of us.