Halfway through a kiss,
Miracle Girls
Tears dropped out.
Because I closed my heart
and distanced myself from you.
5 PM in the school yard.
The ball's shadow is growing tall.
Don't be so quiet.
Whenever we meet in the hallway,
we always quarreled.
Halfway through a kiss,
tears dropped out.
Because I opened my heart
and we understand each other.
Episode 14
Mini Typhoon
Approaching
Hmm, my bangs are getting too long.
I should have it trimmed.
Ugly face.  What an ugly face.
Hey!  What do you mean ugly?
What are you screaming about?
Oops, it's not the same voice.  Sorry.
That's weird..
Ugly face, did he say?
You can't laugh.  You're my twin.
I bet somebody was kidding.  I bet you were staring at yourself.
No way.
But his voice was just behind me.
Nobody else was around.
Aside from the guy you shouted at?
Yeah.
I've been thinking it might have been telepathy.
No way.  That's too farfetched.
You think so?
Mikage, you want me to take over?
Why?
I mean...
I forgot to buy garlic.  Tomomi, can you..
Forget it!
Fine, I'll go.
See you.
Hey, wait.
Darn Tomomi.  She wouldn't believe me.
Are you OK, kid?
What's wrong?
Stupid kid.
Garlic.
Garlic?  She stinks.
What was that?
Hey Mikage, how much garlic did you throw in there?
The whole pack, so about thirteen.
We've got school to go to tomorrow.
It's more delicious with more garlic.
Mom has to go to work tomorrow too.
Mom, cheer up.
People mess up once in a while.
But it still doesn't make sense.
The contents spewing out of a canister I hadn't even touched.
The cap was on too.
Could that be telekinesis?
No way.
There's been strange things happening these last few months.
Like towels falling of the shelf all at once.
Scissors and curlers are misplaced.
Everybody else says it's probably just me.
Is it really me?
Mom, you're getting too tired.
Really.  You should take a break.
You're right, but I have reservations tomorrow.
Regular customer?
She's a lawyer, so she's very busy.
She wants me to do her hair, so I can't take the day off.
Tomomi, can you bring me the towel?
Sure.
And then can you mop the floor?
You must always be smiling in the salon.
You look like you've been forced to help.
Sure.
Hello.
Hello Mrs. Kobayakawa.  I've been expecting you.
I'm in a rush.  Can you do the usual?
Sure.  This way please.
Yu-chan, go read some books.
Garlic breath.
Can you use telepathy?
If you can hear my voice, answer me.
You talked to me, didn't you?
Garlic breath.
Hey, you kid.
Mom, she's...
Tomomi, don't bother Yuhei-chan.
But I wasn't doing anything.
I'm sorry.  He's a very nervous child.
He doesn't like talking to strangers.
I'm sorry.
Was that him?
No way.
Really?
Honestly.  Not just telepathy, he can use telekinesis too.
There he is.
I saw that kid too.
Did you?
That brat must've called me ugly.
Calm down Mikage.  I'll try him.
Yuhei-kun.
So it's him.
It's me.  You saw me in the beauty salon.
Oh, so you're twins.  Bummer.
You talk so differently.
Shut up.  Mind your own business.
You're such an ugly kid.
And you too.
See you, old hag.
What's his problem?
Now that you mention it, when the towels fell,
or the shower broke, Yuhei-chan was around.
But he can't be responsible for any of them.
It's impossible.  He was away from those things.
But he can.  With telekinesis.
I bet it's him.
You slammed into the wall tripping over a cord?
Yeah, I know.
He's still a kid, so he doesn't know how to control his power.
Why don't you two teach him?
About that, he's an obnoxious brat.
Noda-kun.
It's him.
Oh, are you interested in ESP?
Kageura-sensei..
You're buying "Challenge to Husbands, 365 Recipes"?
Don't try to evade my question.
I'm not at all.
Where am I?  Who am I?
It's him.
I can't stop!
Hold it.  Why did you do that?  Even if you're just a kid, you can't get away with that.
You have lousy taste.  Can't you find any better ones?
That was my teacher.
Why should I have anything to do with Kageura?
Oh, just a teacher?
Can't you talk with your mouth?  Not with telepathy.
That brat.
Mikage.
Tomomi.
Mikage, did you see Yuhei-chan come this way?
Over there.
Where?
So this house is?
Let's go, Tomomi.
Aren't you worried?
About what?
Why he's doing tricks on us.
Because he's a stupid brat.
No, but maybe he was trying to say something to us.
I'm home.
Yu-chan, welcome home.  I'll be home late again.  I'm sorry.
The dinner is in the fridge.  Use the microwave to warm it.
At 9, get changed to your pajamas, brush your teeth, and go to sleep.
Don't use any fire.
Somebody...
... help me!
Just now...
Yeah, I heard.
He said help.
Yuhei-kun!  Yuhei-kun!
He's not answering.  He should be in there.
Mikage, let's go in.
But...
What the heck?
Yuhei-kun!
Are you OK?  Are you hurt?
What happened here?
Where did you get in, hag?
The front door was unlocked.
You did all this, didn't you?
Where is your mom?  Is she away?
Leave me alone!  Don't come into my home!
Yuhei-kun, listen to me.  We were..
Just get out!
Let's go, Tomomi.  Why should we waste our time on this brat?
Mikage.
Mikage.  Mikage, wait a bit.
Forget it, it's useless.
What a brat.
But wouldn't he get lonely being by himself in a big house like this?
That doesn't mean he can fool around with the power.
You're right, but..
Leave him alone, and he'll get bored soon.
Stupid brat.
Mikage.
That was that you, wasn't it Yuhei?
I know it.
Answer me.
Hold on, Mikage.
We can't leave him like this.
I bet he's been doing the same trick everywhere else.
Don't you care about other people?
I bet your mom's worried too.
Mom doesn't care about me.
She's working every day.
She doesn't care about me.
That's not true.
Leave me alone!
Gotta stop him!
How?
Yuhei-kun, listen to us!
Yuhei-kun, calm down.
We're gonna get killed if we stay here.
Then lets teleport out with Yuhei-kun.
Where are we?
Mikage, why did we end up here?
How should I know?
It must be Yuhei-kun's power.
At least there's nothing breakable up here.
Don't worry.  We've got you.
Really?
Honestly.
We won't let go of you.
I...
What is it?
I always thought it was only me.
That has this weird power.
You ladies are the same, aren't you?
Look who's calling us ladies.
He was calling us ugly hags until a bit ago.
Mom's getting married again.
You'd get lonely, wouldn't you?
So you've been agonizing over it by yourself.
Doesn't matter now though.
How long are we going to stay up here?
Right.
This is teleportation, right?  Teach me how.
You're too young for this.
You're a bit too heavy.
Lousy aim.
Yuhei-kun, is your mom coming home late?
I guess so.  Why?
We better clean up this room before she comes home.
You're not telling mom?
There are things other people shouldn't know.
But promise us you won't play tricks again.
I will.
So, how are we going to explain this?
Like we played tag?
That's a good one.  You're 'it', Tomomi.
Say what?
Mom's out for a date tonight.
I see.
She's in for a surprise when she comes home.
What does it take to break this many things?
Mom, actually...
Yuhei...
Yuhei, don't do it again.
OK!
So, he was feeling lonely because his mom's getting married?
That's one thing, but he must've thought he's the only one.
That's right.  All ESPers are lonely.
You don't sound that way.
I hope Yuhei-kun will be cheerful like Mikage.
Right.
I hope he won't play tricks again.
It could get worse.
What's going on?
Miracle Girls here.
All right, who signed me up for track and field?
Not just that, you're signed up for literature club and travel club too.
That wasn't me!
Next on Miracle Girls,
"Irregular Cherry Front"
No way!  There's two Mikage's!
Original air date April 9, 1993.
Whatever we do,
there has to be both of us.
Matsunaga Tomomi ...Fujieda Nariko
Matsunaga Mikage........Nagai Noriko
Even if we had a fight,
There has to be both of us.
Noda Yuhya...........Yamaguchi Kappei
Kurashige Hideaki...Shiozawa Kaneto
Miracle Girls on internet http://www.tcp.com/doi/miracle/miracle.html
There are days when kindness is so close that you can't see it.
Miracle Girls Original Soundtrack Sony Records SRCL 2574
Shinichiroh Kageura...Ken Yamaguchi
Daijohji Rumiko.................Sakuma Rei
Even if we know better than anyone else.
Yamagishi Kouhei.......Nobuh Tobita
Editing, timing, subbing and additional translation by Miwa
When we can't say ``I'm sorry,''
Subtitled by Studio Hooseki.
www.miwasoft.com/hooseki
we send out feelings through the little fingers.
Going over the tears,
we want to be honest to ourselves.
'Cause the sky deserves a rainbow.
Whatever we do,
there has to be both of us.
Two of us
are better than one of us.