Halfway through a kiss,
Miracle Girls
tears dropped out.
Original Work by Nanami Akimoto
(Serialized in "Nakayoshi")
Character Design:
Yoshihisa Sekine
Series Coordinator:
Hirokazu Kobayashi
Because I closed my heart
Filming Director:
Hieao Shirai
Art Director:
Takashi Nakamura
and distanced myself from you.
5 PM in the school yard.
Music:
Michiru Oshima
Filming Director:
Hieoao Shirai
The ball's shadow is growing tall.
Opening Song
"Halfway Through a Kiss, Tears"
("Kiss no Tochu de Namida ga")
by GARDEN
Don't be so quiet.
Ending Song
"There has to be Both of Us"
("Futarijanakya Dame Nano")
By Dio
Whenever we meet in the hallway,
we always quarreled.
Halfway through a kiss,
Producers:
Shinichiro Maeda,
Yuhko Sasagawa
& Ken Yorita
tears dropped out.
Because I opened my heart
Created by
Nihon TV
and we understand each other.
Produced by
Japan Taps & ASATSU
Episode #24
What? Senpai's Sweetheart?
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One..
- Therefore...
- Bye!
Stop, younger Matsunaga. My class isn't over yet.
Don't you wanna go home too?
Where your loved one waits for you.
Sure, I do...
Rika-san is so pretty.
Yeah? You think so too?
So, I'd like to go see my loved one too.
I see. So you want to go see your loved one. Fine, go ahead.
Loved one? What did you mean?!
I'm not telling you!
No improper conduct with opposite sex! Stop, younger Matsunaga!
So she used teleport. I'll catch them some day.
I'm not a taxi service.
So don't think I can come whenever you call me up with telepathy.
Sorry.
Perfect.
So you gonna visit him again?
You bet. He's so happy to see me.
But I think he might get annoyed if you go every single day.
That's not true. He told me my cooking's delicious.
I made too many fried squid rings. You can have them.
Senpai, how does it taste?
Delicious.
Oh good. Would you try niku-jaga?
Note: Niku-Jaga = beef and potato stew
I'm trying it for the first time.
Niku-jaga...
I see what you meant by first time. It's got a very fresh taste.
I hope Kurashige senpai doesn't get food poisoning...
I better go.
Thank you for coming.
Can I come again tomorrow?
I don't mind, but what about your club and other things?
That's nothing really.
I'll bring you more food tomorrow.
Take care.
Yes, come in.
She was so pretty. Who was she?
I bet she's Kurashige-senpai's sweetheart.
I was just kidding.
No way. It's 'cause Tomomi said something weird.
There's no way senpai would...
It wasn't her.
Good afternoon.
Where did you get the roses?
My friend came by and dropped them off.
The blond lady? What about the sandwich?
This one, the friend who just left.
Another foreign lady?
I brought you food, but I guess you're stuffed.
I think you're misunderstanding something.
What misunderstanding?
Mikage.
Kurashige-senpai became some womanizer..
No way. Not him.
'Cause, I saw them.
I can't believe it.
I just can't understand the tastes of science buff..
Are you taking it seriously?!
You heard that?...
Hello, this is Matsunaga. Oh, Kurashige-senpai.
You want to talk to Mikage?
I see. Thank you. Bye.
Sorry, senpai.
Mikage, you should've talked to him.
I should've guessed. I should've told her everything.
I know it was hard to tell her that.
Mikage's been flying high ever since you came back.
They're in Japan as exchange students.
Oh, they are?
Their boyfriends in high school back in London
dumped me all the letters and gifts to them.
So, I've been getting in contact with each of them.
I knew it. Mikage always jumps the gun.
Make sure you tell her that.
Yes, I will.
Oh, I forgot my hat.
I see. So they're exchange students. Figures.
Mikage..
What?
I know you'll get mad at me,
but I don't think it's a good idea to stick around with him all the time.
Why?
Well, you see.. Overdose of affection isn't that good, right?
Got it. I think I know what you're trying to get at.
You're right. I've been going high.
I was too happy to see him back.
Tomomi, what's wrong? Tomomi!
Nothing. I'll go take a batch.
Senpai, are you really going?
Yeah. It's been my dream to study in London.
I got it from my relative in London. You can have it.
Are you sure? Isn't it important to you?
Morning, Mikage.
Mikage... Mikage?
Tomomi, did you see her too?
Yeah.
Why was she crying?
Mikage...
I'm so confused.
Good bye, Mikage-kun.
Senpai... Senpai...
Senpai, don't go!
Younger Matsunaga. No sleeping in my class.
Sensei, I see your nose hair sticking out.
Don't try to evade me! As punishment, you solve this problem.
You already finished?
Not bad, Younger Matsunaga. This was from
an entrance exam of a national university.
There. I found it under your desk.
You aren't acting like yourself, brooding over. Can't you believe in senpai?
Tomomi, will you? To senpai's room.
Mikage-kun.
Mikage-kun!
You fool! How dare you skip out class!
As a punishment, you clean up the science building!
Matsunaga-san.
Hello, Mikage Matsunaga-san.
You got it all wrong.
Wrong?
That Kurashige and I are in love.
Don't worry. Kurashige and I are just friends.
My sweetheart back in London is Kurashige's roommate.
So I was dropping by to see Kurashige to hear about my boyfriend.
Kurashige's worried because you misunderstood everything.
I see.
How are you doing, Kurashige?
That's not nice. Don't look so disappointed.
I brought her too.
Hello, senpai.
Mikage-kun.
I'm really sorry about everything...
Thank god you found out the truth.
So her experiments always blow up.
Blow up?
Last year's club budget was used up just on repairs of the club lab.
Why do you have to tell her everything?
Sorry.
Just to straighten up the fact, half of it was Kageura-sensei's explosions.
You're right.
He's a really nice man, isn't he?
Can I ask you something?
Sure.
Why were you crying in senpai's room yesterday?
Oh, you saw me?
Wow, he's handsome.
His name is Harry. He loves basketball.
I always had to wait for the practice to finish.
After that, we always went to see movies or dance.
I came to Japan just as Kurashige got there,
but Harry always talked about Kurashige in his letters.
I wish I could see the letter.
But... He hasn't written recently.
Not a single letter for the past month.
That's when I got a call from Kurashige.
So, senpai got something from Harry for you?
Yeah. I got so emotional when I got it.
So Kurashige was comforting me. I'm sorry, Mikage-san.
I see.
He doesn't write me, but I guess he wants me to write.
Men are always so selfish, aren't they?
So, that's the story.
Tomomi, let's teleport to London.
Eh... why?
Come on, let's go. We made it last time. We can do it again.
What do you wanna do over there?
We'll go see Harry and tell him to write letters.
I want to do what I can do for Liz-san.
I thought I'd choke to death...
So this's Kurashige-senpai's...
This picture's just before he left for England, wasn't it?
I bet he was remembering about you looking at this.
What's wrong?
What are you going to do? You gonna tell Liz-san about Harry-san?
I can't do that.
You're right.
You knew already?
Harry started going out with her because he got lonely after Liz went to Japan.
Does Liz-san know about it?
No, but I'm sure she noticed.
She was concerned about him not writing any letters.
I wanted to tell her, but I couldn't get around to.
I know how you feel.
What's this?
Liz forgot it.
No, she left it here.
Tomomi!
Liz-san!
Are you sure about this?
Have you noticed already?..
I have.
I did, but I just couldn't give up about him.
That's why I went to see Kurashige everyday.
But everything's OK now.
Liz-san.
I gave this to Harry as his birthday gift.
I'll write a dear John with this.
So she already knew.
Will she be OK though?
I'm sure she'd find a great boyfriend again.
You're right.
Can I keep this watch for good?
Sure. Take good care of it.
Senpai, what would you like for tomorrow's lunch?
Lunch?!!
She seems to know about our power.
And every time we see her, it's raining. She's gotta be a rain woman!
Next on Miracle Girls,
"Strange Rain Passing By."
We'll teleport to your room tonight!
Whatever we do,
there has to be both of us.
Ending Song
"There has to be Both of Us"
("Futarijanakya Dame Nano")
By Dio
Even if we had a fight,
There has to be both of us.
There are days when kindness is so close
that you can't see it.
Even if we know it better than anyone else.
When we can't say "I'm sorry,"
we send out feelings through the little fingers.
Going over the tears,
we want to be honest to ourselves.
'Cause the sky deserves a rainbow.
Whatever we do,
there has to be both of us.
Two of us
are better than one of us.