Halfway through a kiss,
Miracle Girls
tears dropped out.
Original Work by Nanami Akimoto
(Serialized in "Nakayoshi")
Character Design:
Yoshihisa Sekine
Series Coordinator:
Hirokazu Kobayashi
Because I closed my heart
Filming Director:
Hieao Shirai
Art Director:
Takashi Nakamura
and distanced myself from you.
5 PM in the school yard.
Music:
Michiru Oshima
Filming Director:
Hieoao Shirai
The ball's shadow is growing tall.
Opening Song
"Halfway Through a Kiss, Tears"
("Kiss no Tochu de Namida ga")
by GARDEN
Don't be so quiet.
Ending Song
"There has to be Both of Us"
("Futarijanakya Dame Nano")
By Dio
Whenever we meet in the hallway,
we always quarreled.
Halfway through a kiss,
Producers:
Shinichiro Maeda,
Yuhko Sasagawa
& Ken Yorita
tears dropped out.
Director:
Takashi Anno
Because I opened my heart
Created by
Nihon TV
and we understand each other.
Produced by
Japan Taps & ASATSU
Translation by
Naoki Mizutani
Additional timing and editing by
Karis Fra Mauro.
Episode 17
Jet stream
to Memory
I can't find it!
It's gone!
Tomomi, where did you put my bead bracelet?!
Don't know.
You better! Why you cleaned up my room?
'Cause, it was a mess.
No, it wasn't.
You seriously didn't see the bead bracelet?
No, I didn't. Besides, when did you buy that?
Don't you remember it? It has little bell on it.
I can't remember.
There.
That's pretty old picture.
This bracelet. Don't you remember it?
Nope...
Hey, Tomomi!
Besides, was it really in your room before I cleaned it up?
I bet you left it somewhere.
Tomomi, let's use the final way.
What final way? What are you up to, Mikage?
We can teleport to the bracelet.
But I look everywhere and it's nowhere.
If we end up somewhere other than your room, get ready for consequence.
Now, this's a big room.
That's weird. Why did we end up here?
I bet you weren't concentrating, Mikage.
Did too.
Then is the bracelet here?
I don't know.
Then how come we ended up here?
How should I know?!
Damn, where are we?
That's my bracelet.
Mikage!
What is it, Mikage?
A little girl took away my bracelet.
Why?
I don't know.
Nobody's around.
Where did she go?
Fast runner, isn't she?
We'll go after her.
Don't tickle me.
Are you sure it was your bracelet?
I'm positive.
Then why did she have it?
Tomomi?
What's up?
Didn't they chop down that zelkova tree years ago?
Huh?
Right?
A cat?
Tomomi, gotta find the girl first.
Why do you have to tell me what to do?
Mikage, watch out for the cars.
Yeah. See you later.
Wait.
Are you OK?
Where did she go? Where are we?
That's the elementary school.
It's been awhile.
It hasn't changed since we were there.
Which way?
Where did she go?
We haven't eaten snacks. Besides we were running all over.
I'm getting a bit hungry.
Why are we running around here?
Are you saying it's my fault?
Not really.
Then how come your bracelet was there? Hold it!
That's cute.
Lucky you, Mikage-chan.
Daddy got us this. Tomomi-chan's got the same.
My daddy brings us just cakes.
You have good daddy.
She's not around.
What? Found her?
Found crepe shop! I'll have chocolate banana! What's wrong, Mikage?
You're such a...
Look at her!
Yeah, she's got chocolate banana!
I meant, my bracelet!
Mikage, watch out!
Are you OK?
Where did she go?
Lost her again.
Mikage!
Let's go!
Bye.
Where are you going, Mikage-chan?
I'm not telling you. Bye.
What is she? A monkey?
There she goes.
You go, Tomomi.
Here we go.
One, two...
You're so heavy. Go on diet, Tomomi!
Oh yeah? I should be slimmer than you.
At any rate, we'll teleport to the bracelet again.
Watch out!
Mikage!
That was close one.
I preferred the ball.
Are you OK, obachan?
Say what?
What is it, obachan?
Who is?!
You are. Did the ball hit you?
We're OK, boys. Thank you.
Stop that!
Did you see a girl? She runs real fast and has yellow bracelet.
I know.
You do ?
She went that way.
Thank you, you two. Let's go, Mikage.
Bye, obachan!
HEY!
Bye, pregnant dress!
Those stupid brats...
Now, now. It's only an innocent trick.
How innocent?!
Those kind of kids wouldn't do any good even when they grow up. I know they will.
OK, sure. But one of them was really cute.
You got real bad taste.
Really?
Where am I? Who am I?
She went this way, right?
Why should we trust those stupid brats?
Remember, they called me obachan. They gotta be blind.
Mikage...
Which way did she go? Gotta find her or it'll get dark soon.
Tomomi, do you see her that way...
I'm sorry. I was reading book, so I didn't notice.
It's alright. It's my fault. You're very good boy.
I'm looking forward to seeing you in ten years. Be careful.
Thank you, lady.
Say, did you come from that way?
Yes.
Did you see a girl with yellow bracelet?
I was reading book, so I'm not too sure, but I think a girl making a bell sound went by.
It's her!
Yes, let's go.
See you. Be careful.
What a mobile kid.
Dead end?
Where's she?
She crossed here?
She's gotta be ninja...
I won't loose to her.
Tomomi-san?
Let's go.
Eh, what?
Hey, Tomomi, hold it!
Don't worry.
Where is she?
There she is.
Want to swing?
I can let you if you can lend me that.
No bracelet, no swing.
Gimme.
No. I can't.
You can have my daddy's restaurant's free smorgasbord ticket.
No!
Fine, I'll throw in the special dinner show.
NO!
What do we do, Mikage?
About what? I'll tell her to give it back to me.
But looks like she really likes it. It's too cruel.
But...
No!
Stay away!
Now, you can't run! Now, lend me!
Don't!
Those voice?
Who was that?
Mikage, did you see that? She could be...
Mikage! Mikage!
Gimme!
No!
It's broken. It's not my fault!
Mikage!
Tomomi!
My bracelet...
Wait, Mikage! Where do you think you're going?
Are you sure you don't wanna go after the girl?
There. You can have mine.
Are you sure?
Yeah. It's your's.
Thank you!
Let's go.
We're home!
Yeah!
Come on, hurry.
Smile, Tomomi, Mikage.
Say cheese.
Yeah, I gave my bracelet to Mikage.
That's right. Thanks. I was so happy.
Now, let's go find the bracelet together.
What happened here?!
Mikage, what do you think you're doing?!
I thought it might be in your room.
You bet it's not!
Besides, how can you make this much mess just trying to find the bracelet?!
But...
SHUDDUP!! You clean up the mess by yourself!
You can't do that.
What's your problem?
Nothing...
Miracle Girls here.
Mikage, where did you go in midnight?
I was playing with the unicorn.
Unicorn?
Tomomi, let's fly to London in dream.
Next on Miracle Girls,
"Unicorn under Moonlight."
Sempai, I'll see you in my dream.
Whatever we do,
there has to be both of us.
Even if we had a fight,
There has to be both of us.
Ending Song
"There has to be Both of Us"
("Futarijanakya Dame Nano")
By Dio
There are days when kindness is so close
that you can't see it.
Even if we know it better than anyone else.
When we can't say "I'm sorry,"
we send out feelings through the little fingers.
Going over the tears,
we want to be honest to ourselves.
'Cause the sky deserves a rainbow.
Whatever we do,
there has to be both of us.
Two of us
are better than one of us.