Halfway through a kiss,
Miracle Girls
tears dropped out.
Original Work by Nanami Akimoto
(Serialized in "Nakayoshi")
Character Design:
Yoshihisa Sekine
Series Coordinator:
Hirokazu Kobayashi
Because I closed my heart
Filming Director:
Hieao Shirai
Art Director:
Takashi Nakamura
and distanced myself from you.
5:00 PM in the schoolyard.
Music:
Michiru Oshima
Filming Director:
Hieoao Shirai
The ball's shadow is growing tall.
Opening Song
"Halfway Through a Kiss, Tears"
("Kiss no Tochu de Namida ga")
by GARDEN
Don't be so quiet.
Ending Song
"There has to be Both of Us"
("Futarijanakya Dame Nano")
By Dio
Whenever we met in the hallway,
we always quarreled.
Halfway through a kiss,
Producers:
Shinichiro Maeda,
Yuhko Sasagawa
& Ken Yorita
tears fell out.
Director:
Takashi Anno
Because I opened my heart
Created by
Nihon TV
and we understood each other.
Produced by
Japan Taps & ASATSU
Translation by
Naoki Mizutani
Episode 15
Irregular Cherry
Front
What are you doing?
I didn't mix them in right order.
Remember you promised you wouldn't do any experiments home!
Do I have any choice? I can't mess up in the membership drive tomorrow.
I'm black all over.
Jeez...
Just wait till you lose it.
She hasn't stacked any blocks for a while.
Damn Tomomi, couldn't she at least wake me up?
It stopped.
What was that?
Yikes!
Lemme out!
Mizuno, come on!
Done.
Why are you locking me up?!
We're sorry, Matsunaga.
With you doing experiments  , we could lose all our potential new recruits.
We'll let you out once the membership drive is over.
Those four will lose out on other clubs.
Now, they sure are dumb.
Matsunaga-san...
What am I doing here?
We wish we knew!
How did you get out?
Get out?
Mikage-kun! Mikage-kun!
Wa-wait! We're sorry!
Let's do it together!
I have to... I have to...
Where is she going?
Who cares. Let's get the new members in before she comes back.
Oh wow.
Can I do the same?
Come on and have a look!
If you sign up now, you'll get to go to a movie with the hope...
of the track and field, Yamagishi-kun.
No way. Let's go.
Wait up!
There.
Thanks you. Did we get any new members?
The girl members will double.
Then will you throw in chocolate chip and mint ice cream?
If you can increase the member by five times.
That's not fair.
Really, Mikage-chan? You really want to sign up for track and field?
Waitsec, Mikage. What about the chem club?
Chem club? But I have to join the track and field.
Are you feeling OK?
What's wrong with me joining the track and field?
Eh, nothing at all.
At least if you can fill out the form.
I will.
There. See you later.
Wait, Mikage!
What happened to her?
When an object that weigh 40 kilo fall for 3 meters, the shock of landing will be 2.3G.
The human bones should be able to withstand up to 4G in vertical shock...
Forget it!
Ow... Gotta hurry.
Did you decide on the club?
No. I'm still trying to decide if I want to join...
Not another failure. It's theoretically perfect.
Hey, Younger Matsunaga, did you get any new members?
I don't know!
You fool!
If the club is shut down, we wouldn't be able to do experiments as we like!
When did you circle around?!
I didn't know!
What's going on?
We should've made flashy experiments like Matsunaga's.
Do you want to expose our shame to the new recruits?
But if this keeps up, she'll get steamed.
I knew it! Nobody's around!
Alone atop the hill decorated by lilac, I wait for the prince.
All by myself, all by myself... by Rumiko Daijoji.
What would you like, Matsunaga-san?
Don't tell me you want to sign up?!
You have a good collection of British literature, don't you?
Yes. But I haven't seen many people interested in British literature.
Not just literature, but everything about England. Then see you later!
Hold it, Matsunaga!
Lemme out!!
Did you remember to lock the window?
It's perfect.
Did you see that?
That was Matsunaga-kun...
If you try lock me up again, I'll sue you guys for illegal confinement!
Where are you going?
I'll go see how she's doing.
But it's almost time for the second run.
Come and fetch me when it's my turn.
Now, the club is history.
But that sure looked like Matsunaga.
Even the clothes were the same.
Towel.
Sure!
Oh, so you're doing the club work.
Of course.
Then why did you sign up for the track and field?
Who did? Me?!
You must be joking!
Why should I join up to a club with stupid Noda as president?!
I'm from the travel club. I'm collecting for the pool.
Travel? Me? Where?
England, wasn't it?
England?
I don't what you are up to, but I, the club president, won't let you.
You signed up for the literature club too?
I don't know.
Don't play ignorant!
You are the only one who'd wear such shameful lacy clothes!
Somebody's gotta be disguised as me and is signing up to all these clubs!
But it was you who signed up for the track and field.
I'll catch this joker!
When I find her, she'll take it!
Did you find her?
What's wrong?
Tomomi!
Tomomi! Did you find her?
Mikage!
There's two Mikages?!
Tomomi! Who is she?!
Hold it! Why are there two of you?!
I'm Mikage! She's fake!
What do you mean? I'm Mikage!
What's going on here?
Quiet! What are you screaming about?
Shoot!
Hey, Matsunaga! Hold it!
Why did you run when I said stop?
Why did you stop?
Stop, Younger Matsunaga!
Hey, Matsunaga sisters, why do you run?!
I swear both of them were Younger Matsunaga...
Mikage Matsunaga-kun, where are you? Come out. It's no use hiding.
Come out, Younger Matsunaga!
Somebody, hold me tight. Hold my heart trembling in love.
What do you think you're doing?
Please, let me hide out here.
There you are, Younger Matsunaga!
Stop, Younger Matsunaga!
Club president?!
I see. I get it.
Hold it!
Stop!
There you are, Matsunaga-san!
Why is Daijoji after me?!
Hey, Tomomi!
What are you doing? It's almost time.
Noda-kun, did you see Mikage?
If you find her, tell me. She's in big trouble.
God.. Gotta find her quick!
What about the track and field?!
Now where's stupid Noda?
Hold it!
What the...
Mikage-chan, did you see Tomomi-chan?
Younger Matsunaga, why did you run away?!
Now I'm safe.
There! Matsunaga-san, why do you have to interfere with me?!
Mikage-chan, did you see Tomomi-chan?
Damn Tomomi...
Mikage, Tomomi was looking for you.
Weird girl.
Did you see Younger Matsunaga?
She went that way.
Will you knock it off?!
And will you give up?!
How dare you lie? Just you wait till the next exam.
Hold it right there, Younger Matsunaga!!
But she just...
What are you doing?!
What's the...
Stop, Younger Matsunaga!
You ruined the literature club!
Knock it off!
Hold it!
Stop!
Damn, lost her again. Younger Matsunaga, where are you?!
You ruined everything!
Now the membership drive is all screwed!
Behind you, Mikage.
Hi, you're late because you were watching the flower, too?
If we ran, we could make it.
I saw the flower last year, too.
I saw the flower last year, with Kurashige-sempai.
Miracle Girls here.
Tomomi, where are you going? Why are you running?
The red shoes I've got on are making me run!
Tomomi, stop!
Next on Miracle Girls,
"Spring Wind Express."
How far do I have to run?!
Whatever we do, there has to be both of us.
Even if we had a fight,
there has to be both of us.
Ending Song
"There has to be Both of Us"
("Futarijanakya Dame Nano")
By Dio
There are days when kindness is so close
that you can't see it.
Even if we know it better than anybody else.
When we can't say "I'm sorry,"
we send out feelings through the little fingers.
Going over the tears,
we want to be honest to ourselves.
'Cause the sky deserves a rainbow.
Whatever we do, there has to be both of us.
Two of us are better then one of us.