Halfway through a kiss,
Miracle Girls
Tears dropped out.
Because I closed my heart
and distanced myself from you.
5 PM in the school yard.
The ball's shadow is growing tall.
Don't be so quiet.
Whenever we meet in the hallway,
we always quarreled.
Halfway through a kiss,
tears dropped out.
Because I opened my heart
and we understand each other.
Episode 8
Occasionally Tears
Morning.
That's bad.
Hey, quit laughing.
Hey, Tomomi.
What is it?
What are you doing?
I was sending telepathy.  Did you get it?
No, I didn't.
So what did you tell her in telepathy.
That I loved her.
You're kidding.
I am.
You idiot.
Noda, you really are an idiot, aren't ya?
You finally noticed?
Sorry, we're just idiots!
I'm late!
Stupid Tomomi!  Why didn't she wake me up?!
Mom!
Watch out!  Run!
That was really a close call, you know that?
Hey...
Mom...
Did you just say mom?
Heading your way!
There is a theory that until approximately 40 thousand years ago,
humans communicated with animals though telepathy.
Is that your theory?
Exactly.
Would you stop these silly talks and get back to the course material?
Hey Mikage.  Can't you at least knock first?
Knock.  knock.
What is it?
Have you ever talked to animals using telepathy?
Have you?
No, I haven't.  Why?
Never mind.
Kageura-sensei.  This is Mikage Matsunaga.
Come in.
Excuse me.
Have you decided to participate in my experiment?
I wanted to ask you a question.
Now that's a rare event.
Can humans really talk to animals using telepathy?
Well?  Can you, Matsunaga?
I asked you the question!
That's right.  I think you know far better than I do.  In the early days of history,
It is believed that people used several means of communication.
Roughly speaking, they fall into three categories: audio/verbal, primitive
symbolic signs, and inter-mental communication, alias telepathy.
However, this ability degenerated as humans evolved.
Why?  It's because of all the tools.
The evolution of tools such as languages and letters led to the decline of telepathy.
On the other hand, animals made a different choice.
Instead of using tools, the animals are using telepathy to communicate, I believe.
Then we can talk, can't we?
Of course, provided that you can use telepathy..like you two.
Fool!
Hello!  Hi!
Hello?
Hey, answer me.  Please?
Good Morning.
Who was that?
Good Morning.  Good Morning.
Come over.  Come here.
Alright!
You stupid dog.
You're the weird dog from this morning.
Did you find mom?
What is it?
I can't understand him.
It was just my imagination after all.
It's only Kageura's theory.
Mom!
So you brought this kitten home?
Kitten?
It's not?
It's got to be a puppy.
Puppy?  No way.
You're a kitty, aren't you?
See?  It says it's a kitty.
He told you that?
No he didn't, but it's a cat alright.
Bummer.  Didn't you say mom?
Forget it.
Nice kitty.  Let's forget about that cold blooded woman over there.
Hey, it's a boy.
You pervert.
What should we do with him?
You're in charge.
What do you mean?  You brought him home.
Sure I'm cold blooded.
What a selfish bum.
Who is?
Who's what?
Who is selfish?
Who?
You said so.
Did I?
Suddenly.  Strange Girl.
Really weird girl.
Isn't this in our neighborhood?
There's an update on the lioness and a cub that escaped from the circus.
A resident of the area reported seeing a lion.  The prefectual police is...
Well, better go to date with the lion.
Too bad you have to work on Sunday.
It's not all that easy running a beauty parlor.
Make sure you lock all the doors and windows.
See you later.
Mom.
Did you hear him?
Did you?
He said 'mom'.
That's Right.  In the shopping district.
Yeah, that pet shop.
It's safe around our home.
Yeah.  But the choppers from the TV stations are flying all over.
What about your place Noda-kun?
Hey, say something other than mom.
The lion is heading north.
Might be injured and dangerous.
Increase the patrol in the north half of the city.
Ensure the safety of the citizens.
There it is.  The lion.
Good job.
Keep it up.  We got her.
Hey, really?  Mikage, turn the TV on.
They're showing the lion.
The lion?
This is brought to you live.
Mom!
After her!
Target sighted.  Will begin pursuit.
The target is heading east.
So his mom was.
He's a lion cub.
Hey, what's going on!
Can't you fly any lower?
It's too dangerous.
I don't care.
Mom!
Chopper One to headquarters.  We have sealed off the area completely.
Will begin capture of the target.
Headquarters, roger.
This is the park where the lion is.
It is now completely sealed off.
With the presence of all the media, the area is quite chaotic.
According to the police briefing, they plan to use tranquilizers,
but they will have riflemen ready just in case.
Are you OK, Mikage?
Hey, watch out!  Fire!
I can hear him.
Yeah, it's him.
I bet they wanted to go back to Africa...
I don't know.
But they probably wouldn't have survived.
How come?
'Cause they've been captive for so long that they probably forgot how to find food.
Why?
Tomomi, don't cry.
I'm not.
I said cut it out.
I'm not crying.
Why are you crying?
I'm not.
Let's go home.
Mom must be worried.
Miracle Girls here.
Yahoo!  We're off for skiing!
I heard there's going to be a storm.
Tomomi, we'll be stranded.
No way.
Next on Miracle Girls, "Snowstorm in Lodge"
Is it true that the snowman lives there?
Original air date Feb. 26, 1993.
Whatever we do,
there has to be both of us.
Matsunaga Tomomi ...Fujieda Nariko
Matsunaga Mikage........Nagai Noriko
Even if we had a fight,
there has to be both of us.
Noda Yuhya...........Yamaguchi Kappei
Kurashige Hideaki...Shiozawa Kaneto
Miracle Girls on internet http://www.tcp.com/doi/miracle/miracle.html
There are days when kindness is so close that you can't see it.
Miracle Girls Original Soundtrack Sony Records SRCL 2574
Shinichiroh Kageura...Ken Yamaguchi
Daijohji Rumiko.................Sakuma Rei
Even if we know better than anyone else.
Yamagishi Kouhei.......Nobuh Tobita
Timed and Edited by Fred Werth.
Typed by Brent Wallace.
Proofed by Tina Barrie.
Additional editing by Miwa.
When we can't say "I'm sorry,"
Subtitled by Studio Hooseki
www.miwasoft.com/hooseki
we send out feelings through the little fingers.
Going over the tears,
we want to be honest to ourselves.
'Cause the sky deserves a rainbow.
Whatever we do,
there has to be both of us.
Two of us
are better than one of us.