Halfway through a kiss,
Miracle Girls
Tears dropped out.
Original Work by
Nami Akimoto
(Serialized in "Nakayoshi")
Character Design:
Yoshihisa Sekine
SeriesCoordinator:
Hirokazu Kobayashi
Because I closed my heart
Filming Director:
Hisao Shirai
Art Director:
Takashi Nakamura
and distanced myself from you.
5 PM in the school yard.
Music:
Michiru Ohshima
Filming Director:
Hisao Shirai
The ball's shadow is growing tall.
Opening Theme
"Halfway Through a Kiss, Tears."
By Garden
Don't be so quiet.
Ending Theme
"There Has to Be Both of Us."
By Dio
Whenever we meet in the hallway,
we always quarreled.
Halfway through a kiss,
Producers:
Shinichiro Maeda
Yuhko Sasagawa
Ken Yorita
tears dropped out.
Translated by
Kei Fujioka
Director:
Takashi Anno
Because I opened my heart
Created by          Nihon TV
Subtitled by
Studio Hooseki
and we understand each other.
Produced by
Japan Taps & ASATSU
Fan Subtitle.
Not for sale or rent.
Episode 11
Watch Out for the Time Flow
Let's call it the day.
Oh!  OK.
Any comment, professor?
Is there anything in there?
We'll never know till we open it up.
We've barely started to scratch the surface.
Wait!  Wait!  Who are you?!  Tell me!
Mikage, wake up!
Are you OK, Mikage?
It's the dream again.
Yah.
We've been seeing it all the time.
Oh, they're excavating the old grave mound in the park again.
Really?
The archaeological team from R University is heading the survey...
Tell me.  Who are you?
Help!  Help!
Mikage.  Mikage.  Mikage.
Mikage, can't you hear me?
What happened to you?
Matsunaga.
I appreciate if you stopped chatting with your sister telepathically during class.
I'm sorry.
Don't tell me you're reading my mind...
I'm not thinking about those tadpoles!
What're you staring at?  Don't look at me!  Stop!
Teacher, stop the nonsense and get back to the class.
Don't look at me.
She left?
Well, she had her bag.
I don't think she was feeling good though.
She looked dazed.
Mikage, are you there?
Oh, she's home.  Thank god...
My body feels so hot.
What's going on?  Tadpoles on every single page.
Mikage, what's wrong?  Are you OK?
The doctor said it's probably just a cold.
The fever hasn't gone down yet, right?
I gave her medicine though...
What's this?  A slate?
Looks like a fireball to me.
It's gotta be a bug.
No, it's not.
It sure looks strange.
What did she draw, really?
May I?
I see.
Sarashina, what about the picture?
It looks like a "magatama".
"Magatama"?
An accessory the ancient people used to wear.  See?  There's a hole here.
They put string through here, and used it as things like necklaces.
Really?
Accessory?
Yeah, I think.  My uncle's an archaeologist.  Wanna talk to him?
Umm.
Hmm!  I think it's a picture of a "magatama."
After all?  Is there anything else you can see in this picture?
"Magatama" was a very popular object for decoration.
So, there's nothing much I can pick up from just this.
Professor, is this the "magatama" you're talking about?
That's right.
By the way, we found that "magatama" from the grave mound on Mount Kokura.
Unlike last time 20 years ago, this time it's a full-scale excavation.
Mikage...  Mikage...
What happened to you?
What's going on?
Mikage, answer me...
Mikage, who is that?
Who is she?
What was that dream?
Tomomi, wait up!
I think you're going a bit overboard,
about a connection between Mikage's illness and the grave mound.
I know how worried you're about her, but how come?
I want to know what I saw.
About the woman wearing a red "magatama."
But that was a dream, wasn't it?
That's not true.  Mikage's not into history at all.
There's no way she'd see a dream like that.
There's gotta be some connection with the grave mound.
Wait !
What?  A man?
It seems he was a very rich class rich man.
I think our man was a very happy man who spent his life in luxury.
Luxury?  Wasn't he lucky?
I'm glad you're interested in this.
I personally often see dreams about ancient people.
I guess it was an easy life in the old days.
I mean in the modern day, it's boring and cramped.
It's sure tough being a man now.
Don't you think so?
Come on, don't be so depressed.
So was there no connection with the grave after all?
I guess that's the case.
The thoughts of people in the past sound romantic enough.
Just like the way you always think.
That's not true.  I'm not talking to you!
Maa, Tomomi !
What's wrong, Tomomi? Are you alright?
My head... Mikage... Mikage's suffering...
Mikage!  Mikage!
Tomomi !
Who is that woman?  Didn't you lead a happy life?
Tomomi, let's go home.  I'm starving.
Mikage.
Mi... Mikage.
Eh, a red "magatama?"
No, I haven't found anything like that around the grave.
Mind you we haven't gone into the casket room.
Casket room?
So, this is the casket room.
There's no red magatama...
Say, you're the man in the dream, aren't you?
Tell me.
Noda!
What're you doing?  Move it.
Aren't ya gonna go to the club?
Sorry, I forgot about it.
How could the club president forget about the practice?
About Tomomi...
What about her?
She didn't show up today, did she?
Thank god.  Her fever's down...
Tomomi, did you see that?
It's that magatama.  She wanted to give it to him.
Scuba diving?!  What happened to you?  The water's still darn cold.
Didn't you say you know somebody who's into it?
Sure, I can get you equipment, but don't tell me you've gone weird, too.
Please?  You're the only one I can count on.
OK. OK. OK. OK?
Now, I'm all set.  Mikage, you can see where the red "magatama" is, right?
Then, teleport me there.
Here we go.
One, two three!
I can't see anything...
Delicious.
You owe me big for this one.
Remember, I told you where to go.
Oh well.
What's wrong, Tomomi?
The lid was closed when I came last time.
Professor Yoshimura said he was a happy man who spent his life in luxury, but that's not true.
He's been there with the memory of a tragedy fifteen hundred years old.
He can't be.  He's a wonderful man.
It's a sad story, but I envy him.
Miracle Girls here!
Tsukasa!
Who is this Tsukasa?
He's an awesome guitarist!  You cheer for him too Mikage!
Next time on Miracle Girls,
"Whirlwind  in  Tomomi"
Noda, don't leave Tomomi alone!
Original air date Mar 19, 1993.
Whatever we do,
there has to be both of us.
Matsunaga Tomomi ...Fujieda Nariko
Matsunaga Mikage........Nagai Noriko
Even if we had a fight,
there has to be both of us.
Noda Yuhya...........Yamaguchi Kappei
Kurashige Hideaki...Shiozawa Kaneto
Miracle Girls on internet http://www.tcp.com/doi/miracle/miracle.html
There are days when kindness is so close that you can't see it.
Miracle Girls Original Soundtrack Sony Records SRCL 2574
Shinichiroh Kageura...Ken Yamaguchi
Daijohji Rumiko.................Sakuma Rei
Even if we know better than anyone else.
Yamagishi Kouhei.......Nobuh Tobita
When we can't say ``I'm sorry,"
we send out feelings through the little fingers.
Going over the tears,
we want to be honest to ourselves.
'Cause the sky deserves a rainbow.
Whatever we do,
there has to be both of us.
Two of us
are better than one of us.