Halfway through a kiss,
Miracle Girls
Tears dropped out.
Because I closed my heart
and distanced myself from you.
5 PM in the school yard.
The ball's shadow is growing tall.
Don't be so quiet.
Whenever we meet in the hallway,
we always quarreled.
Halfway through a kiss,
tears dropped out.
Because I opened my heart
and we understand each other.
Episode 13
x           xMysterious Moving High
Love Pressure
What is it, Mikage?
There's something I wanted to tell you all this time..
You know?
What's up?
Why Noda?
I always...
Wait a minute, Mikage!
Leave me alone.
Noda, I..
What do you think you're doing?
Why were you dating with Noda-kun?
Don't peep into my dreams with telepathy!
What were you trying to tell Noda-kun?
How should I know?
You have a crush on him?
Why should I fall for that ugly piece of junk?
What are you saying?  No, he's not!
I just can't see why you fell for him.
Then how come you had a dream about Noda-kun?
Tomomi doesn't know anything about me.
Mikage doesn't know anything about me.
I hate Mikage.
What?
Why do I have to be in Tomomi's bed?
And her pajamas, too.
What?
Morning!
Morning.
Aren't those Tomomi-sempai's clothes?
That's right.
I always thought Mikage-sempai wouldn't wear Tomomi-sempai's stuff.
Isn't it too convenient if your taste in clothes are the same?
You look great in that.
Morning.
Mikage already left.
You mean Tomomi?
What do you mean, Tomomi?
Don't mix me up with Tomomi.  How long have you been the mother of twins?  I'm me.
I wish she wouldn't confuse me with Tomomi.
What?
Why?
Mom!
What is it?
Look, my hair's short.
It's always been.
Never!  I had it this long.
That's Mikage.
I'm not Mikage?
Then there's no problem, is there?
What do you mean no problem?
Stop muttering nonsense and go to school.
Lock the door when you leave.
I don't wanna go to school this way!
Hey, Mikage-chan!
OK!
Don't do it!
Owww..
Come on, you aren't that athletic.  Don't push it, Mikage-chan.
Mikage?
How come my hair's like this?  I can't go to school looking like this.
I can't let Kurashige-sempai see me like this!  What should I do?
They're getting really bold, aren't they.
They must've thought there's going to be an exam.
So that's why they switched.
No way.  But they're so dumb.  They switched clothes, but didn't change their hair-do.
Therefore, in regards to the question whether the mind can be transplanted like brains...
I'm quite impressed, Younger Matsunaga.
You have come to my class even if you have to switch clothes.  I'm quite happy.
Why is Mikage..
When did you get to school, Mikage?
I'm sorry about last night.
I shouldn't have peeked into your dream.
I'm Mikage!
Mikage, we're in trouble!
I'm in trouble myself, because my hair got shorter.
That's not all.
What do you mean not all?
Stop complaining and come over now!
What's going on?
I don't know.  I'm you, right?
Probably.  And you're me.
I think so..
That means Mikage is me, and I'm Mikage.
No wonder my hair's short.
No wonder this body's dull.
None of your business.  Don't tell me you walked around in that costume.
Now everyone's going to think I've got no taste.
And look at you.  You're in those clothes.
Because I never noticed about this whole thing.
Neither did I!
Gotta think of a way to get through this.
Therefore, in regards to the question of whether the mind can be transplanted like brains...
What?
Why do I have to wear these lacy things?
Oh quiet.  I don't wanna be in these tasteless clothes either.
Say what?
Why do I have to feel nervous?
You were looking at Noda-kun, weren't you?
Did not.
Did too.  So the dream was true after all.
That's dumb.
Matsunaga-san.
Yes?
Did you say something?
Nothing at all.
You gotta be joking.  Why should I fall for Noda?
Hey, Yamagashi, come over!
Hey, your croquette looks good.
Wanna trade with my fried shrimp?
Sounds good.  Wanna trade with me too?
I thought you liked fried shrimp.
No thanks.
Why?
I don't want it.
If you don't want it, I'll take it.
Forget it.
Come on, can't I?
Can I sit here?
Mikage-chan...
It sure feels scary to sit with Mikage.
I'll take that.
What is it?
I thought you hated fried shrimp.
When did you start liking it?
I was trying to scam it off Noda.
What's wrong everybody?
Say, Yamagashi.
What is it?
Weren't they acting funny?
Like how?
You were getting along fine with Mikage-chan.
That's not the point.
I see.  Then I'll take Tomomi-chan.
Hey, wait a sec.
Just kidding.
You!
Don't get steamed!
What is it, Mikage?
There's something I wanted to tell you all this time..
You know?
What's up?
Noda again?
I always... about Noda-kun...
Hold it, Mikage!
Peeping again?
Noda, I...
What do you think you're doing?
You were dating with Noda-kun again?
You were peeping again?  I'm Tomomi now.  So that's the way, isn't it?
No it's not!  It's Tomomi's body, but Mikage was dreaming!
What are you talking about.
So you were after Noda-kun after all.
No kidding.  Your body must have made it up.
I don't believe this.  There goes another dream into waste.
No way!  Why should I wear this?
Do we have any choice?  You're Tomomi for now.
Why should I date Noda for you?
All right.
Change into this.
I might do what you don't want me to do.
What do you mean?
I might kiss him.
I'll get you if you do that.
After all, it's your body.
You'll be late.
Noda deserves to wait.
I don't want him to think I'm lazy!
A girl in love can beat the boundaries of time and space, I suppose..
Shaddup and do it.
Stop being bossy.
Mikage.
OK.  I'll do it.
What was that?
Must be static.
That's weird.
Tomomi's late.
Oww..
Tomomi.
Noda-kun.. Morning.
Hey, what are you scared of?  Lemme shake you off.
But..
Oww..
Tomomi!
Are you OK?
I'm OK.  Now where's Tomomi?
But aren't you..
I meant Mikage was supposed to come too.
She's coming too?
You know, Noda-kun?
What is it, Mikage?
Sorry, Tomomi.
I see, you were thinking about Mikage..
Mikage.
I didn't know you could use a PC.
Just a bit.
Where's Mikage?
I don't know.
There's a call from Noda-kun, but I wonder why for Mikage.
Is To.. Mikage home?
I see.
Where are you, Tomomi?
Mom's worried.
Tomomi!
Welcome home, Mikage.
Same to you, Tomomi.
Hey!
Morning.
What's holding you?
Sorry!
Move it.
Shaddup.  Let's go!
Hold it right there, Noda!
Wait!
Miracle Girls here.
There's strange things happening at mom's beauty salon.
Looks like a boy is responsible for this.
Is he an ESPer?
Next on Miracle Girls,
"Mini Typhoon Approaching"
Gotta teach him how to use the ESP.
Original air date April 2, 1993.
Whatever we do,
there has to be both of us.
Matsunaga Tomomi ...Fujieda Nariko
Matsunaga Mikage........Nagai Noriko
Even if we had a fight,
There has to be both of us.
Noda Yuhya...........Yamaguchi Kappei
Kurashige Hideaki...Shiozawa Kaneto
Miracle Girls on internet http://www.tcp.com/doi/miracle/miracle.html
There are days when kindness is so close that you can't see it.
Miracle Girls Original Soundtrack Sony Records SRCL 2574
Shinichiroh Kageura...Ken Yamaguchi
Daijohji Rumiko.................Sakuma Rei
Even if we know better than anyone else.
Yamagishi Kouhei.......Nobuh Tobita
Editing, timing, subbing and additional translation by Miwa
When we can't say ``I'm sorry,"
Subtitled by Studio Hooseki.
www.miwasoft.com/hooseki
we send out feelings through the little fingers.
Going over the tears,
we want to be honest to ourselves.
'Cause the sky deserves a rainbow.
Whatever we do,
there has to be both of us.
Two of us
are better than one of us.