Halfway through a kiss,
Miracle Girls
Tears dropped out.
Original Work
by Nami Akimoto
(Serialized in "Nakayoshi")
Character Design:
Yoshihisa Sekine
Series Coordinator:
Hirokazu Kobayashi
Because I closed my heart
Filming Director:
Hisao Shirai
Art Director:
Takashi Nakamura
and distanced myself from you.
5 PM in the school yard.
Music:
Michiru Ohshima
Filming Director:
Hisao Shirai
The ball's shadow is growing tall.
Opening Theme
"Halfway Through a Kiss, Tears."
By Garden
Don't be so quiet.
Ending Theme
"There Has to Be Both of Us."
By Dio
Whenever we meet in the hallway,
we always quarreled.
Halfway through a kiss,
Producers:
Shinichiro Maeda
Yuhko Sasagawa
Ken Yorita
tears dropped out.
Director:
Takashi Anno
Because I opened my heart
Created by
Nippon Television
and we understand each other.
Produced by
Japan Taps & ASATSU
Episode 3
Wind
Towards London.
Sensei, sayonara
Sayonara
Don't take any detours.
What's wrong with you, Matsunaga?!
Why haven't you blown anything up yet?!
Are you feeling OK?
I'm fine.
No way.
Go see the nurse!
I'm not satisfied with that little fizzle!
I'm not satisfied at all.
Damn.
Ouu...
Don't!
You can't do that!
But there's nothing I can do.
You can't put pictures like that in the grad book.
Here are the requests from the grads to put your pictures in the grad book.
Here!
But those pictures are too much.
What's too much?
Sensei, do you hear anything?
Be quiet!
You're getting on my nerves.
ehhh...?
Come on, stop her, won't you?
How come?
'Cause! She wants to put pictures like these in the grad book!
Look at them.
Let's see.
They are good pictures.
No they are not.
But, you're always like that.
That is so.
No way.
If your going to use my picture, please use better pictures.
What pictures?
Huh?
Mikage, what's wrong?
Mikage?!
Tomomi?
Tomomi-chan?
Matsunaga-imouto. What is she doing here?
I have no time for that!
Odd, I don't hear anything.
I should switch ears.
Oh, I hear the voice of the earth!
That's strange...
What are you doing here?
Mikage!
Do you want to see senpai?
I hear the laugh of the earth!
I don't believe it,
you fell down the stairs?
Does your back hurt?
My Heart hurts.
Mikage, I'll fly you.
You don't want to walk home, do you?
So, I'll fly you home.
Bummer, I thought you meant London.
You dummy. No way I can do that.
I should have known.
Mikage-kun!
Huh? You're not Mikage-kun.
Where did Matsunaga-imouto go?
Tomomi-kun, I saw Mikage-kun enter this room.
This is weird.
It's not weird.
Ahh, it's a UFO!
UFO!
Pardon me.
Matsunaga-ane!
Good-bye!
Wa..wa..wait a minute...
too late...
I wanted to see the UFO too.
Dear, how long will you be home this time?
I'll have to head back to the Flentze branch in a couple of days.
Oww, that hurts.
Who's there? Oh, Mikage.
Don't startle us.
You've done it again.
How many times do I have to tell you not to come inside with your shoes on?
You'll leave scratches all over the floor.
Dear, you don't look well.
I feel a little weak.
I see.
What was that all about?
Mikage fell down the stairs.
She didn't look too well.
Oh my!
Hi.
Kurashige-san,
you're here to study, aren't you?
Yes, and you?
My relative is ill and I'm here to look after her.
See you again.
Sure, good-bye.
It's papa. I'm coming in.
The sensor we just set will pick up the bio activity wave and display it here.
The flower's wave doesn't match with an known species of plants.
Does that mean...
There's a 99% chance its the flower of the legend.
All that's left is to find my younger twin sister, Emma.
My family?
I have lied whenever you asked about your family, that I was looking for them.
My family...
The people who abandoned me...
However, I can't leave you behind without letting you know.
Mikage, what are you doing?
Mikage, mommy will be mad at you.
Mi..ka...
It's not this one.
Noda-kun.
Mikage's missing.
Yeah, she went to the library.
Why would someone skip school to go to a library?
Tomomi-chan, aren't you gonna finish that?
What, Noda-kun?
Tomomi-chan, are you OK?
Yeah, why?
Cause... you know?
Matsunaga-san?!
Yes!
Ahh, there you are.
Did you bring some other pictures?
The page with you is the only one not done yet.
The page with me?...
Why did I ever trust you? Silly me.
OH NO!
I'm sorry! I forgot!
I need them pretty quick. The printer is coming to pick them up soon.
Don't forget them tomorrow.
yes.
I guess I'm not doing too well.
Senpai!
OUCH!
"Noda-kun?", right?
Is something bothering you?
Tomomi, you're acting weird today.
Really?
What is it?...
What was that? I saw Tomomi.
Mikage, what's going on? What are you doing?
I've seen a ghost around here.
A ghost, get it?
Tell me if you see one.
sure.
She might be my daughter.
The flowers seem to resonate with our power.
Resonate?
Our wavelengths match.
I see. Our wavelengths match.
At that moment, I was thinking about the time I met senpai.
I see, that's why.
It was awesome.
I don't know how to put it, but tears just kept on pouring out.
Mikage, I think I know how much you like senpai now.
I know, I'll go see senpai!
The power of Love will beat time!
Distance is nothing!
She gets stuck on this so fast.
Grandpa, is the legend coming true?
Yeah!
The Legend of the Twin Princesses.
Twins divided by light and shadow.
When the shining flowers come under the sword of light, the source of power is created...
And the twins of light shall unleash their power of heaven from the flowers.
They will rain gold to make the new ruler shine.
The new ruler shall drive all shadow from the world by the light.
There must be something resonating. Track the source of the other wave.
The world will be in a state of eternal enlightenment.
Impossible! Mikage-kun?
Senpai!
You always surprises me.
Shuddup!
Aren't you good at sewing?
What's wrong with that?
Damn!
She sure pulls off a lot of stunts.
I almost had the source pinpointed.
I saw you walking with a ghost.
But she wasn't my daughter.
She always surprise me!
Oh shoot!
What's wrong?
Come with me, OK?
I don't want to.
Sarashina-san will be mad at me.
It's got nothing to do with me.
No way!
Fine!
I can run for it, but you...
Alright.
Miracle Girls here.
If I knew I'd see senpai,
I would've worn something better.
You never had any decent ones.
OK, I'll get the best one at a bargain.
and Tomomi, also title Next on Miracle Girls, "Bargain Typhoon."
Why do you need a strategy just for a dress?
Whatever we do,
there has to be both of us.
Even if we had a fight,
There are days when kindness is so close that you can't see it.
Even if we know better than anyone else.
When we can't say "I'm sorry,"
Translated by:
Naoki Mizutani
Typed and edited by ALKIII.
Timed by Fred Werth.
Proofed by Tina Barrie.
Subtitled by
NT-Anime.
we send out feelings through the little fingers.
Going over the tears,
we want to be honest to ourselves.
'Cause the sky deserves a rainbow.
Whatever we do,
there has to be both of us.
Two of us
are better than one of us.