Halfway through a kiss,
Miracle Girls
Tears dropped out.
Original Work
by Nami Akimoto
(Serialized in "Nakayoshi")
Character Design:
Yoshihisa Sekine
Series Coordinator:
Hirokazu Kobayashi
Because I closed my heart
Filming Director:
Hisao Shirai
Art Director:
Takashi Nakamura
and distanced myself from you.
5 PM in the school yard.
Music:
Michiru Ohshima
Filming Director:
Hisao Shirai
The ball's shadow is growing tall.
Opening Theme
"Halfway Through a Kiss, Tears."
By Garden
Don't be so quiet.
Ending Theme
"There Has to Be Both of Us."
By Dio
Whenever we meet in the hallway,
we always quarreled.
Halfway through a kiss,
Producers:
Shinichiro Maeda
Yuhko Sasagawa
Ken Yorita
tears dropped out.
Director:
Takashi Anno
Because I opened my heart
Created by
Nippon Television
and we understand each other.
Produced by
Japan Taps & ASATSU
Episode 4
Bargain Typhoon
Isn't this a cute dress?!
Yeah.
This is the best one recommended for this spring.
Isn't it nice?
sure...
Take a closer look, see this red?
There's a smooth line along the shoulder and all these frills.
There aren't that many other dresses that're this finely made.
That's right.
This is great, maybe I should get it.
56,000 yen.
(approx. $510.00)
So, did it fit?  Wow!
You look very pretty in it, really.
Is that right?
This's the only one in this color.
It's all cotton, so it's easy to wash.  A best buy, I'd say.
But I don't have...
That's no problem.  Just leave a deposit and we'll hold it for you.
This's the only one of this color.
Now, what do you say?
I can't buy it!
Sure, the frills are cute and the color is wonderful, too.
Besides, there's nobody who would look as I would in this dress.
Sure, I love this dress.  Honestly.  I want it badly.
But...
I can't buy it.
I see.
Mikage...Mikage...
MIKAGE!
Don't use telepathy like that, Tomomi.
Well I tried calling you for a time, but you wouldn't answer.
What do you want?
I need some help on the math homework.
Sorry.  I've got something else on my mind.
Something else?
That's right.  A very highly philosophical one.
Fine.  I'll do it by myself.
Tomomi!
What is it?!
You're so cold.  Look how deeply troubled I am.
Can't you at least ask why?
Can I borrow some money?
Mikage?
Whaa...?
I found a really cute dress.
I want it real bad, so can I borrow some money?
Mikage, why don't you ask mom?
Forget that.  She just bought me this skirt.
How much is the dress?
56,000 yen!  It's expensive, but really cute.
It's a beautiful red and has lots of frills.
huh...
Tomomi?
I'll do my homework by myself.
Tomomi!
Darn it!
Nice heading!
hmm...
What's going on?  Did you quarrel or something?
Since last night.
Ohh, Thanks!
That's not fair, Noda.  Me too!
How cruel!  I had to get up early to cook all this.
Mikage, what are you ticked off about?
It's none of your business!  Stupid Noda!
She found a dress she wanted to buy, but it's too expensive for her.
How expensive?
56,000 yen.
What's that?
I don't get it.
I don't need your understanding!
I'm sorry.
Tomomi, there's no need to apologize to that idiot.
That's right.  No need to say sorry to him.
Noda?  where's the ball?  What's keeping you?
Sorry!  See ya.
I prefer the egg a little sweeter.  See ya.
We're short-handed today, can you work the counter?
Do you remember what I told you?
Yes.
Then, good luck.
Excuse me.
Oh, may I help you?
A fish burger, one potato, and a woolong tea.
Yes, that was a fish burger, one potato, and a woolong tea, right?
By any chance are you on a diet?
This combination is for that, isn't it?
yeah...
Then, you should forget the potato and take the salad.
Potatoes are high in calories, I'll change that to a salad.
No, potato!
Definitely not.
Listen...
That'll be 580 yen.
(approx. $5.30)
We're terribly sorry.
Forget it!
I was just trying to be helpful.
Matsunaga-kun, can you go over to the kitchen?
Yes.
Manager!
Now what did she do?
I was trying to make a special burger, but it didn't work.
You're fired!
Tomomi.
Is this the dress, Mikage?
Yeah.
It's very cute.
Forget it!  No way!
You said yes before.  Now give it up.
I don't want to.
But this is the only way.
Quiet.  What's going on?
Sensei, we'd like to help you on your experiment.
What?  Really, Matsunaga?
Sure, but here's the bill.
50,000 yen?
(approx. $455.00)
Now then, what are you going to show me?
Tomomi will receive these cards.
Teleportation?
Ok, Tomomi?
yeah...
At last, I get to see this.  Now, show me your powers!
Mikage, are you sure you want to do this?
Mikage!
Be quiet.
Here we go.
Teleport complete.
What was that?
So, it was teleporta....
That was only a trick!  Stop fooling around.  Show me your true power!
I'm sorry!
Mikage, this way!
Good thing I didn't pay in advance...
Listen...
You're starting to make it look like I've been harassing you.
Let me tell you something.
Tomomi.
Mikage.
What are you doing here?
I was just looking for you, but I ended up here...
So you like that skirt?
Yeah, but this is expensive too.
Listen, hear this...
Then me too!
All right!
And this section should be...
Yes!
What are you doing?
Bargain strategy.
Bargain strategy?
We'll begin training tomorrow.
huh?
Now, I gotta do something about these guys here...
Here's the main floor.  There are three entrances.
We'll go in from the back door.
Why can't we just go in from the front?
That's the height of folly.
Hey, do you actually know what it means?
This side should be less crowded.
I don't know.
The dumbest thing you can do.
Oh Noda, I bet you did well on that essay.
Oh, not really.
Yamagishi-kun, come here.
What for?
Just move it!
Sure.
Here I am.
Stand at that corner.
I got it.
Is this good enough?
What's she up to?
Don't know.
Mikage-chan, what brand of shampoo do you use?
Don't move!
Sure.
OK.  Now, on the X-day, you will stand here and block everybody else.
What a cheater!
Uh-oh.
And here's the second point, the escalator.
With Noda up front, Tomomi and I will block the way to stop others.
That's dirty!
Owww.
And here's the third floor, the main battleground.
There's no such thing as reason here.
No way.
Don't take bargains that lightly.
Everybody else is your enemy.
No way.
There's no mercy at bargains.
To get around this corner first, we'll have Noda get ahead with Tomomi following.
Using Noda as an anchor, Tomomi will cut the corner and...
Goal In!
What about my skirt?  Hey, Mikage?
Tomorrow, the dress will be mine.
Mikage, knock it off.  You told us to go to sleep early!
Sure.
Holy cow.  I guess Mikage's plan won't work.
This was part of the plan from the beginning.
At any rate, do as I told you to do.
I got it!
Noda, look, cute girls all over the place!
Are you all right?
Yeah.
Where's Mikage?
Ow, don't step on me.
Then stop pushing me!
Don't blame me, tell that to whoever's behind me.
All merchandise is 50 percent off.
Right.
Noda-kun.
Tomomi, here!
Tomomi!
I'll go ahead.
ehh...
Shoot....
Hey, move it!
Mikage?
Hey, where's Yamagishi?!
Tomomi, hurry!
But...
This is nothing!
Let go!
What took you so long?
I was completely surrounded by girls.
Good grief...
No...no...I can't find it...
Here it is!
Tomomi?...Tomomi?
What is it?
Where are you?
It's too scary where you are and I have things I want to buy, also.
Get over here!
No way!
Will you?  I can't find the dress!
I will after I buy this.
No.  Come over now.
Mikage?
Tomomi?
Mikage?!
Mikage?...Mikage, are you there?
Mikage!
Mikage.
Noda-kun, come here.
Tomomi.
Noda-kun.
Where's Mikage?
I can't tell.
OK.
Mikage?
You're late.  Where were you?  Give me a hand.
But...you know...
Let's go.
Charge!
Mikage, did you find it?
Hey, hurry!
I'm losing my grip.
I can't hold on much longer...
Don't rush me.
Here it is!
Mikage?
What's the matter?  You found it, didn't you?
This collar...  I don't like it.
MIKAGE!
Mikage, what was that thing this morning?
It was strange, wasn't it?  It could be the bracelets.
Bracelets?
Our power could have become more sensitive because of the flowers.
If it did become more sensitive, I wish you had noticed the shape of the collar earlier.
Good night.
Geez...
Miracle Girls here.
What do you have against me?
I don't have anything against you.
No way.  Noda-kun saw me in terrible shape.
Next on Miracle Girls, "Mostly Mikage, Partially Tomomi."
Tomomi, how do you play volleyball?
Whatever we do,
there has to be both of us.
Even if we had a fight,
There are days when kindness is so close that you can't see it.
Even if we know better than anyone else.
Typed and edited by ALKIII.
Timed by Fred Werth.
Proofed by Tina Barrie.
Additional editing by Miwa.
When we can't say "I'm sorry,"
Subtitled by Studio Hooseki.
www.miwasoft.com/hooseki
we send out feelings through the little fingers.
Going over the tears,
we want to be honest to ourselves.
'Cause the sky deserves a rainbow.
Whatever we do,
there has to be both of us.
Two of us
are better than one of us.