Halfway through a kiss,
Miracle Girls
tears dropped out.
Original Work by Nanami Akimoto
(Serialized in "Nakayoshi")
Character Design:
Yoshihisa Sekine
Series Coordinator:
Hirokazu Kobayashi
Because I closed my heart
Filming Director:
Hieao Shirai
Art Director:
Takashi Nakamura
and distanced myself from you.
5 PM in the school yard.
Music:
Michiru Oshima
Filming Director:
Hieoao Shirai
The ball's shadow is growing tall.
Opening Song
"Halfway Through a Kiss, Tears"
("Kiss no Tochu de Namida ga")
by GARDEN
Don't be so quiet.
Ending Song
"There has to be Both of Us"
("Futarijanakya Dame Nano")
By Dio
Whenever we meet in the hallway,
we always quarreled.
Halfway through a kiss,
Producers:
Shinichiro Maeda,
Yuhko Sasagawa
& Ken Yorita
tears dropped out.
Director:
Takashi Anno
Because I opened my heart
Created by
Nihon TV
and we understand each other.
Produced by
Japan Taps & ASATSU
Translation by
Naoki Mizutani
Episode 16
Spring Wind Express
There they are! The lead pack is coming!
Who's ahead?
It's Tomomi-sempai after all.
She did it! Move it, Yamagishi!
Tomomi-sempai's leading the pack by miles!
It's OK with you, right Remi?
The national high school marathon will start in a moment.
Would all participants come to the starting point?
Remi!
The moment of truth, huh Remi?
I'll get the picture of the moment you win.
The last sprint was so awesome.
I can't believe you picked up the pace before the goal.
You made me nervous.
I feel so grate.
There.
Thanks.
Don't your legs hurt? I'll massage you.
You, eat this!
Matsunaga-san.
Congratulations, Matsunaga-san.
Sarashina-sempai.
There you go. Open it.
Isn't this Remi-sempai's?
Remi gave them to me before she transferred schools.
She held the record of this race.
I know. I heard she was the hope of the club.
She had the same time as your's.
So, Tomomi-chan had a tie record.
That's for you. A gift for the victory.
Are you sure? Isn't this important memory for you, Sarashina-sempai?
I want somebody who can run to her satisfaction.
I'm sure the shoes would be happy that way.
Or don't you need a gift, because you didn't break the record?
Yes!
I'm sure Remi wouldn't mind if you have them.
But...
Lucky you, Tomomi-chan.
Awesome, Tomomi.
Thank you, sempai.
Nooo!
Matsunaga-san! Matsunaga-san!
Are you OK?
Sure. Sorry.
What was that? Tomomi?
Nothing. Just felt dizzy.
I see.
Remi!
Remi, what are you doing there?
Nothing.
You've got time to kill, don't you?
I'm waiting for my date.
No way. See ya.
Kageura-sensei, it's no use putting on gadget like that.
Now come and get me.
Don't you underestimate your teacher's power.
Remi, give your best shot!
Don't you lose.
Here we go, sensei.
Beat him, Remi!
Good luck!
She's awesome, isn't she?
I haven't met her since she transferred school. I wonder how she's doing.
How's the size?
Seems to be OK.
Alright, 2nd generation!
Looks good on you.
You think so?
Who is that?
Tomomi!
Tomomi! Tomomi!
My feet are...
What's wrong, Tomomi?
My feet are moving by themselves!
What's wrong, Matsunaga-san?
Feeling playful?
Oy, Tomomi!
Noda-kun!
Yamagishi, stop her!
Tomomi, what have you been...
Mikage!
What's up?
Tomomi!
Noda!
What's going on?
Stop me!
I can't run.
The goal is too far away.
Who's that?
I'm so bored.
Somebody, help me!
Tomomi!
Is she really not joking around?
You dummy. She just finished running a full marathon.
She can't do that as a joke.
Tomomi!
You dummy!
Sorry!
What's wrong, Tomomi?
I wish I knew.
It stopped.
Tomomi, are you OK? Where are you?
The railway crossing by 3rd Street.
What?
I can't. I can't run anymore. What do I do?
Go for it, Remi.
Break your record, will you Remi?
I can't!
How far do I have to run?
I'm out. What's with you, Tomomi?
Get on the back. We have to stop Tomomi-chan.
Sarashina-san?
Hang on tight.
Yes!
I never thought you had a secret like this.
How can I be a role model student without a secret or two?
Is Tomomi-chan headed this way?
Yes. She's heading that way. Straight ahead.
Twins are so interesting.
I mean you can say with certainty that she's going that way.
What?
I mean, I envy twins!
Are you sure we're heading the right way?
How should I know? You said to take a truck!
I can't run. I'm out of breath.
Remi-sempai?
I'll be expecting a new record.
Give your best shot, Remi.
There she is!
Tomomi!
Tomomi-chan! Tomomi-chan, are you OK?
I'm thirsty.
Tomomi, knock it off or you'll break down.
But I can't stop.
I can't run. I'm out of breath.
I'm sorry, everybody.
That's me... in that race...
Tomomi!
Tomomi-chan!
Remi!
Remi, aren't you? It's been awhile. How have you been?
OK. And you, Risa?
Fine. I'm so surprised.
They're Mikage-chan and Tomomi-chan, one year junior to us.
With those shoes, this course, and at this spot.. You look miserable.
Just like I was.
Remi, how could you...
You know? I was so dumb.
Remi...
I'll go.
Hey you! Hold it!
Stop! Why did you leave the shoes behind?
If you like to run that much, you keep the shoes!
What's the use of running this much?
The wind feels so good.
This feeling...
This was the goal of the race.
There they are!
I always wanted to see Remi make it to the goal. Like this.
Tomomi!
Are you alright?
Remi!
Congrats, for finishing the course.
It took me over a year. Forget the record.
The shoes wanted to come to the goal with you.
Oy, Tomomi!
Tomomi, are you OK?
Tomomi-chan!
Noda-kun!
I'm out.
Are you OK?
What a wimp. Aren't you two in track and field?
The problem was that the truck went the other way.
You dummy. I can run thousand kilo more!
Now, that's impressive. Then, you can carry me on the way back.
No, thanks! I don't wanna die!
Say what?! Watch your mouth!
Hold it you wimps!
Miracle Girls here.
I can't find it!
What did you lose?
The bead bracelet I had since I was a kid!
I don't know.
Next on Miracle Girls, "Current of Memory."
Tomomi, we'll teleport to the bracelet!
Whatever we do,
there has to be both of us.
Even if we had a fight,
There has to be both of us.
Ending Song
"There has to be Both of Us"
("Futarijanakya Dame Nano")
By Dio
Guest Cast
Remi: Yuhko Mizutani
(Assembler in Compiler)
There are days when kindness is so close
that you can't see it.
Even if we know it better than anyone else.
When we can't say "I'm sorry,"
we send out feelings through the little fingers.
Going over the tears,
we want to be honest to ourselves.
'Cause the sky deserves a rainbow.
Whatever we do,
there has to be both of us.
Two of us
are better than one of us.