Halfway through a kiss,
Kissu no tochu de namida ga
Miracle Girls
tears dropped out.
Koborete shimau
Original Work by Nanami Akimoto
(Serialized in "Nakayoshi")
Character Design:
Yoshihisa Sekine
Series Coordinator:
Hirokazu Kobayashi
Because I closed my heart
Kokoro tozashite anata o
Filming Director:
Hieao Shirai
Art Director:
Takashi Nakamura
and distanced myself from you.
Touzakaete itakara
5 PM in the school yard.
PM5/go ji no koutei
Music:
Michiru Oshima
Filming Director:
Hieoao Shirai
The ball's shadow is growing tall.
Ball no kage mo nagai
Opening Song
"Halfway Through a Kiss, Tears"
("Kiss no Tochu de Namida ga")
by GARDEN
Don't be so quiet.
Sonna mukuchi de inaide
Ending Song
"There has to be Both of Us"
("Futarijanakya Dame Nano")
By Dio
Whenever we meet in the hallway,
Rouka de au tabi
we always quarreled.
Kenka shiteta noni
Halfway through a kiss,
Kiss no tochu de namida ga
Producers:
Shinichiro Maeda,
Yuhko Sasagawa
& Ken Yorita
tears dropped out.
Koborete shimau
Because I opened my heart
Kokoro hiraite subete ga
Created by
Nihon TV
and we understand each other.
Tsuji aeta kara
Produced by
Japan Taps & ASATSU
Miracle Girls #26
I'm going to change schools
What a play, Tomomi!
We can win this game.
Ryoko, it's too bad you can't play.
Oh this? It's okay, I'll get well before the final.
Our school will make the final?
Of course.
It'll be okay because Tomomi is on my team.
That's right.
Alright!
Tomomi nice block!
You bet!
It was just a fluke.
You're the Number One extra player in Japan!
See I did it!
You are Matsunaga Tomomi, right?
Yes.
Umm, what can I do for you?
My name is Takeda, from Kanaria Jogakuin.
Kanaria? ... The favorite for the championship?
Matsunaga Tomomi, you've been scouted.
What??!!
I'm home.
Oh I'm so hungry.
You can eat that.
Mikage, what are you doing?
Of course, you know I'm making food for Kurashige-sempai.
I made it for you and really put my heart into it.
That's a cute cookie, it looks as if it were you.
Don't say such things, it's too much.
It's a wonderful cookie.
Really?
You're gonna be a good wife.
Just kidding!
It's gonna be tough for senpai!
Did you say anything?
Not at all.
By the way Tomomi, how was the game?
Hey listen, I was scouted!
What?
What do you mean what? You know volleyball, I was scouted for volleyball.
What was Tomomi scout?!!
Yeah! A scout had been watching her since the first round.
Really? That's great.
Isn't it? It's Kanajo, that school is the best place to play volleyball.
A scholarship and you don't need to study.
That means, all you have to do is play volleyball.
That's right, I was surprised.
Well that's good. Kanajo's volleyball team is the best team in the area.
Are you gonna go there Tomomi?
No way, I don't have any intention.
Oh yeah, you don't wanna separate with somebody, right?
Come on, that's not...
But finally Tomomi who has only reflexes has a chance.
What do you mean only reflexes, don't say that, it's cruel.
Because that's true.
Ok, I made it. Cute.
Tomomi, senpai will be happy, right?
Those cookies aren't done yet.
Tomomi! Why didn't you tell me earlier?
I watched yesterday's game.
Go for it next game.
Thanks.
Morning Tomomi, Mikage.
Good morning.
How is your arm?
It's getting better. I can take off the cast soon.
By the way, congratulations, you were scouted by Kanajo, right?
What? How do you know?
You can't have any secrets from me.
Just kidding.
Actually I heard from my coach, I was so happy that I told everybody.
I won't go there.
Morning.
A future Olympian has appeared.
Hey everybody, I'm now gonna interview Matsunaga Tomomi.
Everybody please be quiet.
How do you feel now, as Kanajo is a regular
championship contender famous nationwide?
I haven't decided if I'm gonna go or not.
Oh, she is very modest. Just like a champion.
She is truly the future's superstar.
Yeah, Tomomi you're so cool!
Here you go Tomomi.
Thank you.
Even so, talk about popularity!
You are truly very popular.
It isn't nice to my teammates.
No way, they're so happy from their hearts.
Also, it encourages them.
Ryoko.
Hey Matsunaga.
Yes?
Takeda-san.
Okay Matsunaga, listen to him very carefully.
Yes coach.
Thank you very much because I know you are busy.
Oh that's okay, I gotta go.
I'm sorry I came here so suddenly, I feel rather hurried.
So, did you think about that last night?
Are you sure you want to scout me? There are
so many players who are better than me.
You're the one I want, Matsunaga!
Sure, now there are many players better than you, but I believe you have potential.
Potential, eh?
Please come to my school. I will make you a world class player.
Surely.
What can I do?
Noda!
What's up?
Nothing special, but I wanna talk about Kanajo.
Oh that thing. Now you wanna be great at the dash too.
I mean...
I better practice hard.
That's not it...
I've always know about your reflexes, you're a natural at volleyball.
Hey, Noda, why don't you date after club?
What are you talking about?!
See you Tomomi.
I won't lose next time.
You're right, it'll be worse than losing.
Noda...
I've decided.
Thank you for waiting.
Thank you.
Anyway, Tomomi is truly great.
That's right. We've gotta work harder.
Noda!
Are you alright about spending all your time here?
What are you talking about?
Tomomi went to Kanaria Jogakuin.
Mikage.
What happened to make you decide so suddenly?
It's because they're so well equipped and treated.
Are you sure?
Of course I'm sure. Takeda said he'll believe in my potential.
The formal procedure will be after the final, but I'm gonna come here as soon as I can.
Wait, are you really sure? Did you talk to Noda?
This doesn't involve Noda.
I've already decided.
Tomomi.
Sheesh, I've gotta clean my room.
This is...
I feel nostalgia for my junior high school uniform.
I'm home!
What's wrong with you Mikage?
Tomomi. Tomomi!
What happened?
Tomomi please exchange my school for your school!
Why?
Sport's festival...
I was chosen as a relay athlete.
Were you?
So please. It's my wish for my whole life...
Please participate in the relay instead of me?
What?
Alright, a perfect fit.
No, I can't do that.
What are you talking about Tomomi?
Because...
Don't worry, nobody'll ever find out.
But...
I know I've asked you to do such a rash thing.
Mikage.
But Noda will be participating in the class match relay.
Noda?
If I was last he'd pick on me!
Mikage, I understand.
Really?
Sure.
Yes!
Mikage.
See, you're just like me. That's me from anywhere.
You're so well prepared.
Please remember my school friends.
Ack! This guy! That's Noda.
This dummy's full of energy because he's the cheerleader.
It ticks me off!
He looks fine.
Don't talk to him as he's a monster, devil, and my own personal waterloo!
My coed school has so many guys. I'm scared.
Good morning Matsunaga.
G-good morning.
She didn't find out.
Wow! This is the first time I'm seeing a men's
basketball game, everything's different.
That guy is great.
His jumping and running is the best, and the ball looks like it's glued to his hand.
And he looks like he's enjoying himself so much!!
To the right!
Alright!
I got it!
That guy is Noda Yuuya.
Hey Mikage, how do you solve this question?
That question is solved like this.
That's great. You are a genius girl.
How about this one?
It's not like you to study so hard...
It's because I wanna enter the Arudia Fuzoku school.
I wanna go to the same school as Noda does.
What? Noda?
Hey, don't read my mind!
Excuse me.
Tomomi.
Ryoko.
This is it, eh?
I'm a little bit sad you're changing schools, but we're friends even separated, right?
Of course.
See ya.
It's great that Tomomi was scouted by Kanajo.
What's wrong?
Tomomi was saying she wouldn't change schools but then she suddenly changed her mind.
She might have some problem with Noda.
That guy, he probably doesn't even realize it.
I got it!
Tomomi.
What's up?
Are you really sure it's okay?
I can't do anything, because I've already done the formal procedure.
You've forgotten something you've gotta do.
Meet Noda.
Noda.
That was where the results of the exams were announced.
I found it, it's over there!
You've got it Tomomi.
Alright. We're in the same school as of April.
That is...
Are you gonna transfer schools seriously?
Because you agreed with me.
I didn't say you had to go there.
But you said play volleyball seriously.
Stupid! You can do volleyball seriously even here!
That's okay.
Tomomi.
Noda.
Anyway I like my school.
Go for it Tomomi!
We got a triple play!
How come Noda's so hyper?
He's the temporary coach for little league.
I see, we help him with new magic.
Next time on Miracle Girls,
"Miracle by baseball."
We wanna give you a miracle.
Ending Song
"There has to be Both of Us"
("Futarijanakya Dame Nano")
By Dio
Whatever we do,
Donna toki mo
there has to be both of us.
Futari janakya dame nano
Even if we had a fight,
Kenka shite mo
There has to be both of us.
Futari janakya dame nano
There are days when kindness is so close
Yasashisa ga chikasugite
Mienaku naru
that you can't see it.
Sonna hi mo aru yone
Even if we know it better than anyone else.
Honto wa dare yori mo
Wakkate iru noni
When we can't say "I'm sorry,"
Gomenne to ienai toki wa
we send out feelings through the little fingers.
Koyubi to koyubi de kimochi
Tsutae au no
Going over the tears,
Namida o koenagara
we want to be honest to ourselves.
Sunao ni naritai.
'Cause the sky deserves a rainbow.
Sora ni wa niji ga
niau kara
Whatever we do,
Donna toki mo
there has to be both of us.
futari janakya dame nano
Two of us
Hitori yori mo
are better than one of us.
Futari janakya dame nano