Halfway through a kiss,
Miracle Girls
Tears dropped out.
Because I closed my heart
and distanced myself from you.
5 PM in the school yard.
The ball's shadow is growing tall.
Don't be so quiet.
Whenever we meet in the hallway,
we always quarreled.
Halfway through a kiss,
tears dropped out.
Because I opened my heart
and we understand each other.
Episode 12
Whirlwind  in  Tomomi
Mikage!
Rise and shine, Mikage!
Morning.
I hate that alarm.
How come?
When I'm so sleepy and hear such music, I become sleepier.
Oh?  A beautiful melody first thing in the morning.
Doesn't that make you feel like something good is gonna happen?
You'll be late, Mikage.
Ma'am, I want one katsu sandwich !
I'll have a cream bun!
OK !  OK !  One by one.  Don't fight over there!
I'll have...
Wait a minute...
Are you OK?
Whew!
This is the only thing left.
Just one An-pan for the two of us?
I'm sorry.
You just can't be aggressive, can you?
What can I do?  Everything sold out immediately.
Come on, if you don't hurry, the lunch break will be over.
Tomomi.
What is it, Kanazawa?
Wanna go to this place?
Live house?
The girl who was supposed to go with me caught a cold, so I got one extra ticket.
Let's go, Tomomi.
But I've never been to that kind of place.
Honestly?
Yeah?
Then you have to come, Tomomi.
Isn't it dangerous?
No way. It's not that weird place. Come on.
Or is there some other plan?
The plan is...
I don't have any...
Then, it's settled.
Let's meet at Shibuya train station at five.  See ya.
Live house.
Mikage!
Mikage, are you free tonight?
Huh?
Kanazawa invited me to a live house...
Will you come with me, Mikage?
Forget it.
How come?
I'm busy with an experiment.
She said it's really fun.  Let's go Mikage.
Kanazawa invited you, didn't she?  You go with her.
That's not the point.
You're bothering me!!!
Hehe!  That's weird !
Thanks to you Tomomi, I messed up!  Stop whining and go!
I'm late...
Is she gone?
About time.
Kanazawa.
For a moment, I thought you wouldn't show up.
Eh... Uh... sorry.
Ready.  Let's go.
Ah... Ka... Kanazawa, your clothes...
Something wrong with that?
Nothing wrong, but you have make-up on.
If I'm not pretty, I won't be able to meet the band members.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Oh!  There they are.  Come on.
Been a while.
How are you doing?
Great !  She's my classmate, Tomomi Matsunaga.
Good eveni...
Can you let us through?
Kanazawa, are you feeling OK?
I got it !
Tsukasa, here's some donuts that I made.
Ah!  Donuts?  Great.  Thanks.
I can't live without donuts.
Check it out !  Donuts, donuts, donuts!
Yes.
Was it fun tonight?
Sure.
Why don't you come again?
Tsukasa.
Shoot...
See you later.
Take care.
Mikage, what's keeping you?  Come on.
Mikage, come on.
See ya.
Hmm!  Tomomi is acting weird.
She definitely is.
Wow, thank you, Kanazawa.
Good shot, huh?
It's great.
What's wrong, Noda?
Uh... nothing at all.
Hey, Tomomi.
Morning, Tomomi.
What happened to her?
Words or music transcribed by a medium in France are typical types of automatic writing.
Surrealists saw this as a release of the unconsciousness.
...and incorporated into their own arts.
Tomomi. Quit giggling.  I've been listening to that for a long time.
But Tsukasa is so great.
Who is that?
Guitarist.
So who is he?
Matsunaga!
Yes!
Older Matsunaga!
What were you smirking around?
Nothing at all, teacher.
Hmm! Se...cret?
What are you talking about?
Let's see it.
I'm not hiding anything.
That's not true.
What's wrong Matsunaga?
Sorry.
What's this?
So it went to you.
And look what I had to go through.
Sorry.
So he's the guy on the photo?
That's right.  His name is Tsukasa.  He's so cool and so kind.
Some choice you got.  At least he's better than Noda.
What do you mean?
Look Tomomi.  This is the tape of last night concert.
Are you sure?
You bet.
Thank you, Kanazawa.
Tomomi and Kanazawa?  When did they become friends?
You cheater.
Excuse me.
Yes, may I help you?
The tape was awesome.
Right?
The guitar was so outrageous.
Tsukasa's guitar is it.
Look.  I'm carrying around his pick as an amulet.
But I never thought you'd get into it.  I mean...
Come on.  I like this kind of stuff.  Let's go to a concert again.
When is the next one.
Tomomi looks so cheerful.
Let's go for club practice.
Noda, good luck with your workout !
No problems!  I'll break more records again.
Kaboom!  There she goes again!
Mikage hasn't changed a bit.
Hey watch your mouth.  I'm here you know.
What's wrong Mikage?
I'm not feeling good so I'm going home.
Then whose explosion was it?
Must be Kageura.
Where is Tomomi?
What about Tomomi?
Nothing.
Let's go to work.
Hey, 50 laps of dashing.
Tomomi !
Quiet !
What is it?
Don't act surprised!  The music is too noisy.
Was it?
So this is the band?
No, I just wanted to see how other bands are like.
I wish you'd do that with your headphone.
Mikage.
This segment describes the desolate feelings of the poet.
For this poet, what was the home like?  And how did he feel about it?
Now pay attention to the fact,
that this is the home that he has finally reached
after long and treacherous travels, and read it over.
Well then, let us examine the usage of adjectives and adverbs.
Let's see, Kobayashi...
Yes.
Noda, no club activities today?
Yeah.
Let's go home together.
Sorry, I'm supposed to take Yamagishi to a ramen place that I owe him.  Right, Yamagishi?
I see.  See you tomorrow.
Mikage, are you still up?
What is it?
Kanazawa was...
I'm tired because of lab experiments.  Let me sleep.
Tomomi, go to sleep.
Good night.
Tomomi, I got the tickets for the next concert.
Really.
Now you can see Tsukasa again.
Thank you, Kanazawa.
They'll play a new song.
Really?  I can't wait.
Hi !
Ah! It's him.
Oh my gosh!  I can't believe it.
Can I have your autographs, please?
I see.
Wait.  Wait a minute.
That wasn't enough. Tomomi, can I have ...
No.
Cheapskate...
Bleah!
You're going to a concert next week right?
Yeah.
What's so fun about it?
Sounds like fun.
Yah!
Miracle Girls here.
Why is Mikage dating with Noda?
What can we do?  Our minds got swapped.
No way.
Next time on Miracle Girls, "Mysterious Moving High Love Pressure"
I ought to kiss for Tomomi.
Original air date Mar 26, 1993.
Whatever we do,
there has to be both of us.
Matsunaga Tomomi ...Fujieda Nariko
Matsunaga Mikage........Nagai Noriko
Even if we had a fight,
there has to be both of us.
Noda Yuhya...........Yamaguchi Kappei
Kurashige Hideaki...Shiozawa Kaneto
Miracle Girls on internet http://www.tcp.com/doi/miracle/miracle.html
There are days when kindness is so close that you can't see it.
Miracle Girls Original Soundtrack Sony Records SRCL 2574
Shinichiroh Kageura...Ken Yamaguchi
Daijohji Rumiko.................Sakuma Rei
Even if we know better than anyone else.
Yamagishi Kouhei.......Nobuh Tobita
Original script by Arctic Animation.
Script updated by Resub Boy.
Additional editing by Miwa.
When we can't say ``I'm sorry,"
Subtitled by Studio Hooseki.
www.miwasoft.com/hooseki
we send out feelings through the little fingers.
Going over the tears,
we want to be honest to ourselves.
'Cause the sky deserves a rainbow.
Whatever we do,
there has to be both of us.
Two of us
are better than one of us.