Halfway through a kiss,
Miracle Girls
tears dropped out.
Original Work by Nanami Akimoto
(Serialized in "Nakayoshi")
Because I closed my heart
Character Design:
Yoshihisa Sekine
Series Coordinator:
Hirokazu Kobayashi
Filming Director:
Hieao Shirai
Art Director:
Takashi Nakamura
and distanced myself from you.
5 PM in the school yard.
Music:
Michiru Oshima
Filming Director:
Hieoao Shirai
The ball's shadow is growing tall.
Opening Song
"Halfway Through a Kiss, Tears"
("Kiss no Tochu de Namida ga")
by GARDEN
Don't be so quiet.
Ending Song
"There has to be Both of Us"
("Futarijanakya Dame Nano")
By Dio
Whenever we meet in the hallway,
we always quarreled.
Halfway through a kiss,
Producers:
Shinichiro Maeda,
Yuhko Sasagawa
& Ken Yorita
tears dropped out.
Because I opened my heart
Created by
Nihon TV
and we understand each other.
Produced by
Japan Taps & ASATSU
Episode #23
The Secret is Revealed?!
Can I have an ice cream?
Sure.
That's 50 yen.
See ya!
Hey, Tomomi! Aren't we supposed to share it?!
Tomomi!
If you can catch me!
Shoot.
What is it?!
Oops. She found it.
Senpai...
I am Birdman!
I'll get you, Squirrelman!
Birdman, transform!
Meet your fate!
Do you like Alice too?
Yeah, she reminds me of a friend.
Rick says he doesn't get the story so he hates it.
Rick?
My big brother. He likes Birdman better.
So, you're looking after the store?
Yeah!
You like it? But I can't sell it because it's my treasure.
Rick! Rick!
Somebody, help him!
There.
Rick, Birdman doesn't scream. Hang on tight to me.
Senpai... senpai!
He's awake.
Onii-chan!
Senpai, how do I look in the costume?
You look great.
Really?
But you got the role all of a sudden, didn't you?
The girl who got the role was injured the day before, so here I am.
Did you memorize the lines?
Not really.
You're kidding.
Honestly.
Then what are you going to do?
The show's on today.
Tomomi will help me out.
But I'll be fine. This is the last school test in jr. high.
Besides, you'll be watching. Better do my best.
Attention all cast of jr. secondary level play "Alice in Wonderland."
There will be a rehearsal in the gym at ten.
You are to be there ten minutes prior to the start.
Why does a teacher in the senior secondary level have to play the Mad Hatter?
But you fit right into the role.
Now let us begin the rehearsal.
Alice, I'll read you a book.
How wonderful, big sister.
But books without pictures are too boring.
I want to know more about a dream-like land.
I see.
So that's what she meant.
They're twins OK. They're synced so well.
Noda, you gonna leave me out there baking all those octopus balls?!
Sorry.
Is she Mikage-chan's twin sister...
Tomomi.
That's right. It's her.
Cuuuteee~~~
So she has a twin sister.
Why are you staring at me?
Nothing...
What is that? A white bunny?
They look exactly alike.
Stop!
Oops. That was "A white bunny is running in a great hurry."
I wish you wouldn't alter the lines.
If you want to help, do so accurately.
Sorry.
What's wrong with making small mistakes?
It took me half a year to write this up! It's perfect!
Gee, sorry.
And I take it you aren't taking it seriously.
Say what?!
Or don't you remember lines at all?
Not really. How should I remember it all in three days?
Once you took the role, you had to do your best, regardless of the circumstances.
But she insisted I do it.
That's an excuse!
If you're going to do the role, I'd expect you to do it right.
Besides, Tomomi-chan's not a student of this school.
Therefore, she's not involved in the school festival.
Alright! I'll do it by myself!
I won't ask for Tomomi's help!
Damn Daijouji.
What's she going to do?
But then...
What do we do?
Will you still help me?
But that's too risky.
Senpai's gonna be watching the play.
I can't mess it up. See over there?
Nobody would notice if you do it in the PA booth. Please?
Anything for a love, right?
Excuse me.
Yes? Oh you aren't Mikage-chan.
I'm Tomomi. May I see the practice from here?
Go ahead.
Let us resume the rehearsal.
Mikage, ready?
Anytime.
From the beginning again.
But books without pictures are too boring.
I want to know more about a dream-like land.
Will Mikage be OK?
No idea.
She'd start whining soon enough.
How far will I fall?
I must've fallen all the way to the other side of Earth.
Where am I? Where will I be? Australia or New Zealand?
What is so fun, did you ask?
Yes, what is so fun?
Nothing at all!
Can you imagine holding a tea party over and over?
No time to wash dishes.
Is that why you have been playing musical chairs?
She's got everything right.
She must've memorized them during the break.
She'd better. After all, she's the leading role.
Here's to the tea party by fools!
What's going on?..
I'm getting terrified of my own talent.
Oh no. I must've drank too much tea. To the washroom.
What's she doing there?
There she is!
Tomomi-chan!
What is it? You want to date with me?
There's no line like that, is there?
I don't have time for that.
Stop it.
Mikage, what should I do?
Mikage, what should I do?..
Ma-Matsunaga-san, have you gone crazy?
Tomomi, what are you doing?
Sorry! I'll do something about it real quick!
Something is wrong with Mikage.
There might be something about them.
There is said to be this special link between twins.
What link?
A telepathy. Very interesting.
Delicious, isn't it?
You must be Mr. Caterpillar.
I am not. I am Bokuen Hidari,
the teacher of Japanese history for 45 years.
Students, don't smoke.
Tomomi-chan, if you're scared, you can hang onto me.
Help me!
Why are you grinning all the time?
And what is wrong with your stomach? That is so hideous.
How is this then?
Wonderful!
She's doing perfect.
She's a genius after all.
So I have chosen the right girl.
Finally, it's over. Where's Yamagishi-kun?
Tomomi-chan.
Noda-kun.
Aren't you bored?
Don't worry about what Daijouji said.
No problem. But it looks so fun to be in a co-ed school.
It's got this vitality that I don't see in a girls school.
You know, Tomomi-chan, why don't you apply for this school next year?
I think I will.
Where's Tomomi?
Mikage-kun.
Kurashige-senpai!
So you had all the lines memorized after all.
Well... It's all thanks to Tomomi.
Tomomi-kun was? You two are really close to each other, aren't you?
Yes. It's so comforting to be with her.
I think you could do well in track and field.
You think so?
I bet you're a fast runner.
Then, I'll seriously go for it.
Yeah, do. It'll be fun. I know.
I'll go buy yakisoba. Our club's is real great!
Note: yakisoba = fried noodles
Same school as Mikage's, huh?
Tomomi Matsunaga-kun, are you not?
Yes.
I am Kageura, the science teacher of this school.
There has been an alteration on the script of the play.
We need to give the new script to Mikage-kun, but I can't find her.
Will you come with me to get the script?
Senpai!
They said I can have a half an hour break.
Let's go eat something.
I'm starving.
Tomomi-chan!
Where'd she go?
But you two really look alike.
But I'm me, and Tomomi is Tomomi.
You're right, but to us, twins are very mysterious.
Really?
Enough to make me feel that you might have some wonderful secret.
What are you talking about?
I must've got it right.
Hey, Mikage! Seen Tomomi-chan?
I just saw her.
She was heading over to the school building with Kageura-sensei.
Where's the printing room?
Just a little ahead.
But we aren't going up to the roof, are we?
Come with me. We don't have time.
Mikage-kun.
Mikage, what's wrong with ya?
Tomomi, do you hear me?!
Sensei, aren't we at...
What's with her?
Let's go!
Mikage, what's with this teacher?
Where are you?
On the roof.
Tomomi, he's into psychic stuff. Just tell him you don't know anything!
What do you want from me?
I needed to ask you several questions.
What were you doing over in the PA booth?
Tomomi!
Mikage!
Are you OK?
Yeah.
She really came!
What are you up to?
Before I answer that, how did you know where your sister is?
Why? Well...
I'll tell you why.
A telepathy, right?
No. Just an intuition!
That is the most typical telepathy!
Tomomi-chan, are you there?
It's locked.
Don't worry. I'll keep it secret from your friends.
You are mistaken.
What other powers can you use other than telepathy?
I'd love to see you two teleport.
How can we?!
What's he doing up there?!
Noda, gotta break down the door with this.
Would you unlock the door?
The play is going to start soon.
I don't care about the play anymore!
I want to know the truth.
How dare you break the door?
Mikage!
Tomomi!
What have I done?
Mikage-kun!
Tomomi, hang in there.
You're getting there.
Mikage-kun!
Tomomi!!
Oh... they disappeared?!
We weren't dreaming, were we?
You're shivering?..
I'm sorry... for not telling you all the time...
I thought you'd avoid me if I told you the truth...
I didn't want you to avoid me...
What I said before was right, wasn't it?
I don't know how to put it, but I feel that a wonderful thing just happened.
Senpai...
Awesome! You two are really neat! You just got me all excited!
The play by jr. secondary level, "Alice in Wonderland"
will start in a moment in the gym.
Mikage-kun, you better hurry.
The show won't start without Alice.
Thank you, senpai.
Noda-kun, thank you.
Tomomi.
So ESPers do exist.
Let's keep it secret. Just among the four of us.
Are you sure I can have it?
Sure. Will you give it to your friend in Japan?
Thank you.
Come back when you get better.
And is this friend your sweetheart?
Well...
That's weird. He should be on that plane.
I'll be waiting down in the lobby after I get your luggage.
Thank you.
Hey! Kurashige-senpai isn't around.
He arrived already. I just sent Mikage in first.
How come?
Don't disturb them.
Welcome home.
I'm back.
Isn't this Alice?
Senpai, I'll visit you every day!
Mikage, you got a problem!
There's this pretty woman in his hospital room.
No way!
Next on Miracle Girls,
"What? Senpai's Lover?"
We'll teleport to your heart tonight!
Whatever we do,
there has to be both of us.
Even if we had a fight,
There has to be both of us.
Ending Song
"There has to be Both of Us"
("Futarijanakya Dame Nano")
By Dio
There are days when kindness is so close
that you can't see it.
Even if we know it better than anyone else.
When we can't say "I'm sorry,"
we send out feelings through the little fingers.
we want to be honest to ourselves.
'Cause the sky deserves a rainbow.
Whatever we do,
there has to be both of us.
Two of us
are better than one of us.