Halfway through a kiss,
Miracle Girls
Tears dropped out.
Original Work
by Nami Akimoto
(Serialized in "Nakayoshi")
Character Design:
Yoshihisa Sekine
Series Coordinator:
Hirokazu Kobayashi
Because I closed my heart
Filming Director:
Hisao Shirai
Art Director:
Takashi Nakamura
and distanced myself from you.
5 PM in the school yard.
Music:
Michiru Ohshima
Filming Director:
Hisao Shirai
The ball's shadow is growing tall.
Opening Theme
"Halfway Through a Kiss, Tears."
By Garden
Don't be so quiet.
Ending Theme
"There Has to Be Both of Us."
By Dio
Whenever we meet in the hallway,
we always quarreled.
Halfway through a kiss,
Producers:
Shinichiro Maeda
Yuhko Sasagawa
Ken Yorita
tears dropped out.
Director:
Takashi Anno
Because I opened my heart
Created by
Nippon Television
and we understand each other.
Produced by
Japan Taps & ASATSU
Episode 5
Mostly Mikage,
partially Tomomi
It can't be!
To-mo-mi!  To-mo-mi!!!
Senpai! That's cool!!
That's eight spikes in a row!
Tomomi-senpai...!
Nice work!
It sure tastes great after winning.
Sorry to ruin your Sunday.
Don't worry about it. It was a good workout.
Can you come to next week's game too?
No problem.
Huh...?
Where did I put the short jacket.
Going somewhere?
Yeah. For a bit.
A date with Noda?
Your face is drooling all over.
If Noda sticks to your mind, your face could start looking like him.
No way!
Don't scream like that!
Sorry!
I just remembered,
its still at the dry cleaners.
Why not wear something else?
Please, can you?
To Nakayoshi Dry Cleaner.
Forget it.
Pretty Please? I have to rush...
Or else I'll be late for the date, okay!
I don't think there's much difference what you wear on a date with stupid Noda.
Thank you, Mikage!
Huh...??
That's??
Ah!! Oh bummer.
Isn't Senpai around?
Stupid Mikage...
Ah! Excuse me!! I'm Sorry!!
Oh... I'm getting so bored.
AH! It's Tomomi-senpai!!
Done!!
Now all I have to do is to frame it and it's complete.
What's this?
Oh God!! Do I have time to take a shower?!
I only have 20 minutes!!
Noda-kun's going to be mad!
I don't believe this!
I ran out of shampoo halfway!
I'm not going to make it to the train!
One order of teleport please...?
What are you so mad about?
I'm not.
I wish I could be mad.
I beg you!
Geez, if Noda-kun gets mad and leaves, its all your fault Mikage.
Why should it be my fault?
If he's dumb enough to get mad just because you're late, dump him.
What are you doing?!
I'll use my own power to teleport!
Just lend me your little finger!
Damn it, what's holding her?
Hey, you're late.
Noda-kun...
I wish Tomomi-senpai would step outside.
EH!?
What's going on here?
I'm sure she went inside a while ago.
Done!!
Now all I have to do is to frame it and it's complete.
You're back early.
Tomomi, what's wrong?
Something happened with Noda?
Coming!
Hey, is Tomomi-!!
You idiot Noda!
What the hell did you do to Tomomi?!
N-Nothing at all.
Then how come she is crying?!
Don't ask me?!
You laughed?!
I can't believe how dumb you are!
No wonder Tomomi cried.
Really?
Why would she take it so seriously?
You dull meathead!
Girl's hearts are delicate!
What's your problem?!
What is so funny?
Sorry, but the word delicate doesn't go with you! You are definitely not delicate!
IDIOT!!
You don't scare me!
YOU MISSED!!
Bleeee!
I thought she wasn't athletic...
That damn Mikage...
What makes her think she's delicate?!
I'm more delicate than she is!
Tomomi... Tomomi...
Noda wasn't mad at all.
What's the point of brooding over it?
Hey, why are you blocking my telepathy? Stop ignoring me.
Damn that Tomomi...
Matsunaga-imouto.
What about Matsunaga-ane?
You seemed to be conversing with her with telepathy...
I don't know what you're talking about.
I assure you, you'd feel so much better if you tell me everything.
Stand up!
Bow!
Sensei! Sayonara!!
Hey! Matsunaga-imouto! Homeroom isn't over yet!
Stop ignoring me!
And you stop bombarding me with your telepathy!
Oh yeah?! Just stop your whining!
Hey, Noda! I told you that girls are delicate!!
What's the use of scaring her off?!
I'll deal with Tomomi,
so don't talk to her till then!
Understand?!
Next Sunday, 10 o'clock, at the same fountain. Be there, alright?
What's she up to?
Sensei!
W-Who is that?!
Sensei, what're you doing?
Oh, its you.
That's not very nice.
Look what I got for you.
Here!!
What about these pictures?
You wanted to see Tomomi-senpai's pictures, didn't you?
Oh...
Here...
She shot so many spikes. She was awesome!
So, you're a fan of Tomomi-senpai?
Yeah...
You know what? I saw something interesting yesterday...
I'm home!
Why did you clean up my side of the room?
How many times do I have to tell you to not touch anything in there.
Sure it looks like a mess, but I know exactly where everything is.
Noda said he wanted to date with you again.
It's 9 already? You'll be late.
I bet the park is full of couples.
I bet Noda is already there waiting for you.
Why the hell do you have to be so steamed? You ugly face.
Look who's talking, you ugly face!
Don't read my mind!
You're going?!
Yeah, to the Volleyball game!
Tomomi-senpai & Mikage-senpai!
They're both awesome!
Are you okay, Tomomi?!
What's wrong with her?
That was an easy spike.
She must be sick.
Sorry Noda-kun.
Thanks for asking me out, it was fun!
OUTBALL!
Nice Tomomi!
TIMEOUT!
TAG!
Good luck!
GAME SET!
ALRIGHT!!
I decided not to take any more pictures of her.
But you were so into it,
what happened?
S-E-C-R-E-T. It's too good to tell you, sensei.
Women are always hard to understand.
I told you to stop yelling.
Sorry.
Can I help you with that?
Its okay. I want to do it myself.
I feel like giving you a hand.
That's okay, stop!
Don't be so reserved.
I'm not at all.
Miracle Girls here.
HA HA!! I'm so happy!
This must be a miracle!
Never mind him!
We have to do something or the flower on our bracelets will die!
Next on Miracle Girls: "A fine day to have ESP"
Kageura-Sensei gets ESP!
Whatever we do,
there has to be both of us.
Even if we had a fight,
There are days when kindness is so close that you can't see it.
Even if we know better than anyone else.
When we can't say "I'm sorry,"
Translated by:
Kei Fujioka
Timed and edited by Dallas Operator 7G & Fred Werth
Proofed by Tina Barrie
Subtitled by
NT-Anime
we send out feelings through the little fingers.
Going over the tears,
we want to be honest to ourselves.
'Cause the sky deserves a rainbow.
Whatever we do,
there has to be both of us.
Two of us
are better than one of us.