TOEl COMPANY LTD.
GULLIVER'S TRAVELS IN SPACE
When I was thrown into the stormy sea,
I had nothing to cling to,
not even a piece of wood.
"I'm done for!"
How often I thought just that.
But I realized there was
one thing I could cling to:
Hope!
That's right, no matter what happens,
I must not give up hope!
Hey you!
Don't give up!
Hold on to hope!
Hold on!
Little bum!
If you sneak in here again,
I'll have you thrown in jail.
Don't give up...
Hold on to hope...
I never have any luck. Oh well.
Producer: Hiroshi OKAWA
Associate Producers:
Hiroshi ONOZAWA & Yoshifumi HATANO
Screenplay: Shinichi SEKIZAWA
Animation Director: Hideo FURUSAWA
Music: Isao TOMITA
Art Director: Saburou YOKOI
Animators: Yasuo OTSUKA, Makoto NAGASAWA,
Tomekichi TAKEUCHI, Sadao TSUKIOKA
Katsuya ODA, Sadao KIKUCHI, Akemi OTA,
Akinori MATSUBARA, Yasuji MORI
Directed by: Masao KURODA
Watch out!
That was close. You're very absent-minded.
Was that you?
Yes, it was.
You should be more careful.
Well, goodbye.
What?
Stop!
What is it now?
Don't make me angry!
Remember, I saved your life
at the most dangerous moment.
But that doesn't make any difference.
No difference?
Life isn't any fun for me.
Don't give up.
There's always hope.
Hope!
Everybody says that.
But there's no such thing.
Fool!
Look at me.
I was dumped into this garbage can,
and I haven't lost hope yet.
Get out, you little bum!
If you sneak in again,
I'll give you a beating!
Go away, and don't come back!
You're homeless too, aren't you?
Don't be surprised. I can tell.
Well, where should I go next?
Now that's the spirit!
I know! Won't you come with me?
I'll take you to a nice place.
Oh really? Is there such a place?
Trust me.
Come on, follow me.
Wait!
Wind me up! Wind me up!
Oh, sorry.
Oh, you're a Colonel!
That's right. And who are you?
I'm Ted.
Here you go.
Very well then.
What's your name?
Stray Dog Mack, Sir.
Alright, let's go!
A- A-Amusement park
Joyful, joyful amusement park!
Many dreams come true in this place
Where? Where? Right there!
A- A-Amusement park
Joyful, joyful amusement park!
Swinging to and fro, sliding on the slide
Friends in a fairytale world
Are playing, look there!
Where? Where? Right there!
The carousel spins around
It doesn't speak, But knows
What lonely children hope for
Where? Where? Right there
It doesn't move. How disappointing.
Hey, we only have to turn on the power!
- Yeah!
- Nay!
- Aye!
Oh well...
There's the space hall.
- Let's go in!
- Aye!
It's terrible to turn on
the power at this time of night.
Children these days are impossible.
Who is it?
Turn on the lights!
I said, turn on the lights!
And be quick about it!
It was a majority decision!
- Why, you...
- What's going on?
Halt! Wait!
Wait!
- Catch him!
- Wait!
Company halt!
About face!
One, two, three!
Double quick march!
One, two, one, two...
Wait!
The enemy's coming!
Let's split up.
Wait up!
Where did they go? We'll get 'em.
Darn kids.
- Now we got ya!
- Let go!
Oh no! Oh no!
Mack!
Help!
We're falling!
Where are we, Colonel?
I don't know.
Look what I found! Come on!
Wait!
A ghost!
Oh, it's just a house.
- Let's go in!
- Aye!
No, wait!
Those kids have no fear!
What is it, Kuro?
Gulliver!
Oh, you know who I am?
Yes, but I didn't think you'd be an old man.
Everyone gets old sooner or later.
Now young man, what brings you here?
Well... we've...
Fallen!
Fallen?
Yes, we thought we could find
a nice place to play in the amusement park.
But we were found out,
and we escaped on a rocket.
On a rocket?
Yes, it's true.
That's very amusing.
It's not amusing at all!
Now I'll show you something.
Wow, amazing!
Yes. Now look into it.
Okay.
Kuro, raise the magnification to 50 million.
Yes Sir!
So can you see it?
I call it the Blue Star of Hope.
Blue Star of Hope?
I've travelled to many places
since I was young, for instance...
To a country of dwarves...
And a land of giants.
So for my last trip,
I had planned to go to
that star way out in space.
Well? I call it Gulliver.
Please, Doctor. Take me with you.
It took a long time to build it,
and I've aged in the meantime.
I don't think I can.
Let's do it, Doctor!
I can help you.
No! Let's not go!
Don't be such a sissy.
Take me too!
Well... There may be danger and hardship.
I can handle it!
No! Don't do it!
I can't guarantee that we
can ever come back from that star.
But, there's always hope!
Hope?
It's a good word. Alright!
Nay!
- Aye!
Training, training, training!
Training, it's difficult!
Training, even though it's hard,
We must do our training!
The spaceship Gulliver...
will now be leaving
for the Blue Star of Hope.
There may be danger,
hardship, and fear waiting for us.
However, we must never lose hope.
Let's accomplish our
glorious travel of adventure.
And now, my brave men, let's go.
Clouds fly in the Blue sky
Beyond them is the vast universe
Dreams, hopes, and aspirations are there too
The stars are calling us
Go forth, rocket Gulliver!
Go forth, our Gulliver!
We wave goodBye to the Blue Earth
And advance into the vast universe
Our Breast-pockets are small,
But full to the Brim with hope
Go forth, rocket Gulliver!
Go forth, our Gulliver!
- Goodbye!
There.
How odd.
Sit with your back down.
I don't want to sit in this position!
Kuro, get the automatic launcher ready.
30 seconds to take-off.
Countdown!
Alright, unbuckle your seat belts.
- Don't forget your space shoes.
- Yes.
Do it yourself.
This is too hard for me.
Kuro, check the course!
Where's mine?
Let's eat!
What's with this?
No, no, look.
You must eat it this way.
Oh yeah? Here goes.
Behave yourself!
It's okay...
Kuro, switch on the TV!
Meteorites!
Make them stop!
Dr. Gulliver!
My goodness!
What's happening?
The Reverse Time Nebula!
Reverse Time Nebula?
It's a world where time goes backwards.
Kuro, full power!
We're saved.
This is Gulliver. Gulliver.
Please let us know your name.
Doctor, who could that be?
I don't know, my boy.
You fool!
Wind me carefully!
Sorry.
Doctor! The fuel system!
Let's go, Mack.
I'm scared...
Look, over there.
Oh, Mack is missing.
Don't change it. I was watching that.
Hey Mack, what are you doing? Get back!
Oh, I'm being watched.
Where are we?
A good place.
A good place?
Is this the Blue Star of Hope?
Such a small place.
Nonsense.
On this star, any wish can be granted.
- Really?
- Oh yes!
But only one each.
Can I get some real delicious food?
How about you, strange little doll?
Me?
Well, I would like to become a human being.
Being human can be difficult...
Hey Mack,
can I have a little something to eat?
Colonel, be patient.
Please, will you let me
return to my old shape?
I told you just one. I can't.
I know.
Will you grant my wish?
Of course.
Well then, please help him.
- Do you mean it?
- Yes.
Colonel, you look better that way.
Since you are a good boy,
I will grant you another wish.
Oh, well I...
No wish?
Happiness.
Happiness? What kind?
Well I... don't know...
- Ted!
- Yes.
Hey, we're off course.
Adjust steering.
No good! Someone's jamming us!
Jamming?
From spacepoint 0400.
0400, check.
Oh my.
Doctor, they're forcing us
to land aren't they?
We can't escape either.
It's the same signal.
The translating machine!
This is the Space Patrol.
Space Patrol to the crew of the spaceship:
Come out immediately!
Say nay!
- Any record of an animal robot?
- None.
- Any vegetable robot?
I don't understand.
Anyway, submit the record and let them out.
This is outrageous!
Outrageous!
What could they be?
This is an insult!
The princess is coming home.
Oh, it's that spaceship!
Who are they?
Well... we have... just finished...
the examination... of the robots.
You're crazy, all of you.
What do you mean?
They came from Earth,
in the Solar System, isn't that right?
That is correct.
You're the one that saved us aren't you?
Yes, I just happened to pass by.
Then why didn't you tell us your name?
That wasn't polite.
And then your men brought us here by force.
And they gave us those robot tests.
Very impolite!
I am sorry.
As a token of my apology,
I'll invite you to dinner.
We used to live on that blue star.
But the robots that
our ancestors made became wild,
and they drove us away.
We escaped to this star.
But they still come and attack us even here.
We spend every day
looking for a new star to live on.
Welcome, everyone.
How interesting!
Please, come this way.
Here we are.
Now, please help yourselves.
Pardon me, but do you always eat this way?
Yes.
Tell me, what do they eat on Earth?
Well...
Pork cutlets, ramen,
also... curry rice.
And pig bones!
Porkchops, sukiyaki, macaroni, hamburgers...
That's about it.
So that's Earth...
Please, tell us more.
Well, the Earth...
What about it?
Well, let me explain...
This is Earth...
Ichi, ni, san...
One, two, three...
The words of Earth are "ichi, ni, san"
You can count anything, "one, two, three"
24 hours in a day
Seven days in a week
365 days in a year
The ice melts, spring has come
The petals spin from village to town
The sunlight shines Between the Branches
Look, it's pouring through!
However...
The garden is too small
How lonely
In the South Seas, summer has come
According to a legend among the fish,
There is a coral island
Look, it's shining!
However...
There's a frightful BomB
Poor things
Leaves are falling, autumn has come
Friends are there on a street corner,
Singing a chanson quietly
Oh, it Brings Back memories!
However...
The noises are too loud
How sad
Powdery snow whirls, winter has come
In a village, a little fireplace lights up
The children's cheeks are flushed
Look, they're playing!
However...
Their clothes are torn
Poor things
Ichi, ni, san...
One, two, three...
Do, re, mi, fa, so, la, ti, do...
This is the counting song of Earth
Oh, Earth sounds so interesting.
No, it's not interesting at all.
But... it sounds so much better than here.
In this country, science has made
too much progress, and it's a disaster.
Father...
Excuse me.
Your Majesty, what's happening here?
- Do you know?
- I don't.
I want to know what's going on!
Well...
It was 10,000 alpha pi squared years ago.
Wasn't it?
No, 2 over Q times
P times R squared by 3 million...
You're wrong. It was 2 over P...
Pyuru X Peta X Operon ± infiniti
No, it's the square root of gamma
Or was it squared, times 15?
Although we forgot it somehow,
We lived on the Blue Star
The ancestral scientists thought aBout it
Racked their Brains thinking aBout it
Day after day, they thought aBout...
A roBot that could do everything
We can do it! We can make that roBot!
Life would Be easier with that roBot
Life would Be carefree with that roBot
The easy life has come
Almighty science is paradise
Blue Star is paradise
Go to Hell! Go to Hell!
Go to Hell, humans!
The humans are suckers!
They mechanized anything and everything,
And Became so conceited
Now rise, roBots!
Stand up!
We are roBots!
Proud roBots!
I am the king of the universe!
Now rise, roBots!
Stand up!
We are roBots!
Proud roBots!
That's the Blue Star of Hope.
I can't believe it.
No, it's not a star of hope.
It's more like a devil's star.
That's a big disappointment.
It was our own fault for being greedy.
Attention! Attention! This is Space Patrol!
A robot spaceship is approaching!
Father! Father!
- Your Majesty!
- Father!
Attention!
Enemy spaceship is heading Northwest!
Attention, Your Majesty!
It is nearing the palace!
Get the cannons ready!
Fire!
Fire! Fire!
It's all over...
Hurry, Your Majesty!
Yes, Your Majesty, hurry!
Quick! We all must hide!
In here! Hurry!
Mack!
Where's Mack?
Over here.
Let go!
Look! The princess is gone!
What? The princess?
Mack!
Help!
Princess!
Mack!
Mack...
Doctor...
We must save them!
We'll save them, right?
Can you save her?
You'r Majesty, I'm afraid that is impossible.
Impossible?
So you're just going to give up?
But we can't fight robots.
We can't do anything but give up.
But we must try to
help Mack and the princess.
Mack is one of my best friends.
The princess is too.
The people here
don't know the true value of friendship.
Ted, let's go.
Aye!
We must never lose hope.
Alright.
We have everything but drinking water.
What is drinking water?
It's H2O.
H2O? We don't have any H2O.
You don't?
We gave it up a long time ago.
Dr. Gulliver...
Oh, you mean water!
Water is very dangerous here!
Of course...
I don't understand.
You don't understand.
I'm from the Solar System.
An animal from Earth.
I'm a stray dog!
Stray dog?
Yes, a doggie.
Doggie?
Hey!
Recorder robot!
What's that?
You have no record of a doggie?
What a thing to do!
Why don't they know what a dog is?
That's the Gulliver!
Gulliver?
Check it!
Attention all robots!
Attack the enemy spaceship!
Factory robot, begin making more robots!
Immediately!
Oh no! I must try to destroy the factory!
Where's the factory?
A drop in the morning.
A drop in the evening.
"Mamp." Please have a "Mamp."
What? It's a commercial robot.
Gun robots!
Hurray!
All robots!
Charge!
- Ted, are you ready?
- Yes I am.
Kuro, go look for Mack!
More water!
Sure!
Oh no! Help!
Ouch!
Now we only have that boss robot.
Run!
Oh my! I didn't expect this!
No use! Run!
A dead end!
Here, Doctor!
Mack!
What robot are you?
One cup in the morning. Two in the evening.
Mack. Please have a Mack.
Ted!
Good luck!
How rude!
Oh, Ted!
Let's find the princess, Colonel.
One moment.
Is he okay?
Thanks!
Hurry up! Hurry up!
Doctor! We couldn't find the princess!
We destroyed the transistor robots
that were running the boss robot.
Princess!
We did it!
Is she dead?
No, she's not wounded.
Hey, wait!
The princess might break!
Is that better?
My dress!
Wear this for now.
Stand up.
It's cold.
There.
Mack, the people of
Purple Star only appeared to be robots.
They were no more robots than us.
Ted knew it as well as I.
Look, the sun is rising.
Blue Star will be reborn. Just like you.
Ted, thanks to you,
there is hope for this star.
Good morning, Colonel!
Let's go, Mack!
Good morning, Sir.
Good morning.
Mack, come on.
Mack!
THE END