Halfway through a kiss,
Miracle Girls
Tears dropped out.
Because I closed my heart
and distanced myself from you.
5 PM in the school yard.
The ball's shadow is growing tall.
Don't be so quiet.
Whenever we meet in the hallway,
we always quarreled.
Halfway through a kiss,
tears dropped out.
Because I opened my heart
and we understand each other.
Episode 7
Precognition Index,
? Percent
The increase in the sunspot is the highest ever recorded.
Scientists are concerned over its possible effect on the earth.
Why can't you memorize basic stuff like the periodic table?
C is carbon, N is nitrogen, B is boron, O is oxygen and F is fluorine.
C is oxygen, N is boron, B is carbon, and O is...
All wrong!
N is oxygen...
Wrong again.
N is boron.
Wrong.
N is fluorine...
Forget about this and take the supplement.
No way!  The supplement is out of the question!
What does N stand for?
Let's see.  Carbon.
Forget it.  Take the supplement exam.
Out of the question.  I'm going to the amusement park with Noda-kun.
You can go there anytime you want to.
'Cause...  He asked me out.
Not that way.
What are you doing, Mikage?
We'll be late for the train.
We all ready are!
What was that?
That was bananas.
Don't you remember eating those?
That's not the point!
I mean, why did we see bananas?
Oh, you mean that.
Do you know why?
Why should I.
So there's a major traffic jam here...
Hello?!
Why did we see that instead of teleporting?
Don't ask me.
But...
Are you OK, Tomomi?
That's a banana...
We saw bananas in a vision, didn't we?
Darn it, change!  Something's wrong with this traffic signal!
Let's go to the intersection over there.
Come on, Tomomi.
Here we go again.
Did we just see the future?
No way.
Hey, lunch time.
Get up.
Are you alive?
Noon all ready?
The second block just ended.
I feel so drowsy.
How many hours do you have to sleep?
I don't want to take the supplement exam.
If you take naps, you don't have to take the supplement exams?
No.  I'm nodding off because I've studied all night.
Tomomi's not good in chemistry.
A good mentality will get you through the exam.
One good wild guess!  That's what it takes.
And what do you not understand?
This and that section...
What's up?
Can I borrow your PE strip?
I took them home yesterday.
Ouch.  With all that running around in the morning, I forgot them.
Oh well, fine then.
I'll help you go home and get it.
It's all your fault, remember?
What the heck is this?!
You didn't concentrate on teleport, did you?!
Did too!
Oh, Matsunaga-san,
do you wish to hear my piano?
Piano?
My goodness, you are so close to your sister.
Daijoji-san, did you see the goldfish?
Goldfish?  What nonsense.  There is no such thing as goldfish here.
Bye, Dajoji-san.
What silly twins.
This was Meiji calendar 42 December when Yumeji Takeshita was...
I think it was a future vision after all.
Then how do you explain the goldfish?
We haven't gone to a petshop or any other place that might have goldfish...
I guess so...
Out of the way!  Inertia at work!
Ok, Tomomi?
If we can really use this precognition power..
We can become modern-day Nostrodamuses, and see the end of humanity.
I'll be a Nostrodamus as long as it alows me to see the exam.
Tomomi.
What is it, Mikage?
My legs have fallen asleep.
Mine too.
It's got nothing to do with the chemistry exam, but the sunspot is a current issue.
I'll throw it into the exam.  I can't wait to see the students in a panic!
What ecstasy!
Matsunaga sisters!
Kageura- sensei
I'm a married man!
I understand you look up to me, but...I am your teacher.
Furthermore, I love my wife, Lica-chan.
I may sound..  they're gone?  What did they come here for?
The sunspot has not been active for a while.  However, it is becoming active again.
We teleported instead of precognition.
And of all places, we ended up in Kageura's place.  I wonder why?
Why didn't we see the future?
I think there was something important missing.
What could that be?
Only if I knew...
Did you see that?
No doubt about it.  That was precognition.
But how did it come back all of a sudden.
I know, we haven't been sleeping.
Sleep?
That's right, when we saw the vision  for the first time,
and this time, we hadn't had enough sleep.
I see.  Then if we stay up longer...
Let's stay up Mikage.
Let's not sleep at all and be able to control the precognition power!
Both of  you, what are you doing this late at night.  Stop playing and study.
We're playing to get a better mark.
We're doing this to make sure Tomomi will not have to take the supplement exam.
I'm not going to be responsible for what happens, alright?
Stay up.  The night is still long.
For instance, this phrase, `It didn't rain yesterday...
Ouch!
What's wrong Matsunaga-san?
Nothing at all.
There's still a class going on.
Please don't make funny noises.
Yes.
How far did we go?  Then let's go over again...
Good thing I put this thing here.
Ouch!
Well?  Still feeling drowsy?
Of course.  It's getting even worse with this dull rhythm...
If that's the case...
Papa, please come home soon.
I can't handle two adolescence girls by myself anymore.
Hey Tomomi!
Don't push yourself.
Even if you get a good mark, we can't go to the amusement park if you don't feel well.
No problem.  I've trained myself.
See?  Don't push it.
Don't worry.  Noda-kun, do you like cheese?
Sure, I do.
Good.  I was thinking of using cheese for lunch.  Look forward to it.
I sure hope this works.
Don't worry.  We haven't slept for days.
Here we go.
Did you see?
We still don't have control over the vision.
I guess we'll have to stay up again.
I'd rather forget about it.
Don't give up on me.  Didn't you say we'd be a modern day Nostrodamus.
I can make a prediction without any vision.
If we keep staying up, we'll die.
You're right.
Ok fine.
Hey, we're in good shape for it.
If we blow it tonight, best of luck for the supplement exam.
Stop the ominous comments.
Mikage, look out!
This's...
All right!  It's the exam!
There's no need to stay up anymore.
Which one do you think is better?
Who cares.  Let me sleep.
Should I go for all checkers?
Or the stripes are really good too.
Oh yeah, which bag should I use?
Begin.
What the...
If you don't like that, be teachers yourselves!
Older Matsunaga, you can actually solve this problem?
Yes.
That question is the one that is on the college entrance exam.
Is it really?
Sensei, can I leave when I'm done?
Sunspot activity has been on the decline...
Tomomi Matsunaga.  My goodness.  She's got it all correct!  A rare event!
However, she put her answers one answer box below the correct ones.  Being as strict as I am...
She gets NOTHING!
After all those troubles we went though to see the vision...
Let's get this straight.  I'm not gonna be doing all nighters again.
I wish I could go to the amusement park...
Be quiet!
Come on, can't you go with me?
Forget it.
You better hurry or you'll have to take the supplement of the supplement exam.
I see.  It was the sunspots.
Not a chance!  That's too dumb.
Even Tomomi would laugh at me if I tell her that!
How can you be that cheerful before the supplement exam?
I see, so you're also taking the supplement.
What's wrong with that?
Oxygen is H.. wrong.  Hey Noda,
the amusement park is still on, right?
Why should it be?  Are you sure you're gonna make it through the supplement?
Don't underestimate me.  Oxygen is C.
Wrong.  It's O.
He's got it right.
That's rare.
Morning folks.  Are you all ready to give up?  Take your seats.
Sure...
We tried so many all nighters again, but we never saw any visions.
Thanks to the supplement exam,
I got to like chemistry a bit.  I think...
Miracle Girls here.
Can we talk to animals too?
No, not even if we use telepathy.
Then how come I understand what this puppy says?
Next on Miracle Girls: " Occasionally Tears."
A lion ran away from the circus.
Original air date Feb. 19, 1993.
Whatever we do,
there has to be both of us.
Matsunaga Tomomi ...Fujieda Nariko
Matsunaga Mikage........Nagai Noriko
Even if we had a fight,
there has to be both of us.
Noda Yuhya...........Yamaguchi Kappei
Kurashige Hideaki...Shiozawa Kaneto
Miracle Girls on internet http://www.tcp.com/doi/miracle/miracle.html
There are days when kindness is so close that you can't see it.
Miracle Girls Original Soundtrack Sony Records SRCL 2574
Shinichiroh Kageura...Ken Yamaguchi
Daijohji Rumiko.................Sakuma Rei
Even if we know better than anyone else.
Yamagishi Kouhei.......Nobuh Tobita
Timed and Edited by Fred R. Werth.
Typed by Brent Wallace.
Proofed by Tina Barrie.
Additional editing by Miwa.
When we can't say ``I'm sorry,''
Subtitled by Studio Hooseki
www.miwasoft.com/hooseki
we send out feelings through the little fingers.
Going over the tears,
we want to be honest to ourselves.
'Cause the sky deserves a rainbow.
Whatever we do,
there has to be both of us.
Two of us
are better than one of us.