Halfway through a kiss,
Miracle Girls
Tears dropped out.
Original Work
by Nami Akimoto
(Serialized in "Nakayoshi")
Character Design:
Yoshihisa Sekine
Series Coordinator:
Hirokazu Kobayashi
Because I closed my heart
Filming Director:
Hisao Shirai
Art Director:
Takashi Nakamura
and distanced myself from you.
5 PM in the school yard.
Music:
Michiru Ohshima
Filming Director:
Hisao Shirai
The ball's shadow is growing tall.
Opening Theme
"Halfway Through a Kiss, Tears."
By Garden
Don't be so quiet.
Ending Theme
"There Has to Be Both of Us."
By Dio
Whenever we meet in the hallway,
we always quarreled.
Halfway through a kiss,
Producers:
Shinichiro Maeda
Yuhko Sasagawa
Ken Yorita
tears dropped out.
Director:
Takashi Anno
Because I opened my heart
Created by
Nippon Television
and we understand each other.
Produced by
Japan Taps & ASATSU
Episode 6
Fine day to
have ESP
Oh thunderbolts that pirrce through the sky of chaos and shine upon the ocean of possiblity!
That was the instant that life on Earth was born!
Come forth, life! Create a life out of non-life!
Excuse me...
Overseas Carrier Service...
WHAT?
So, it's from the Voodoo Association.
Oh... half of my year's allowance.
Solving the mystery of the mask will be the first step to solving the mystery of Voodoo.  And I will do that.
Therefore, Dawsing is a type of ESP.
With this power, not only undiscovered mineral deposits, its possible to find undiscovered worlds.
I'm currently working on a new method of Dawsing.
It does not involve sticks or stones, but the use of human eyes.
In other words, this is clairvoyance.
As for how I will use it...
But first, let me explain about clairvoyance.  This has nothing to do with clay, get it?
Sensei!
What is it, Daijoji?
I'll take your questions afterwards.
Would you mind stopping all those fairy tales and get back to the course materials?
Thats where things get interesting!
Its not covered in the text!
Of course not!  Do you think this garbage would contain such material?
I am the only one who knows the truth about the world!
Of course, so does Matsunaga.
Don't you know it?!
About ESP powers.
What're you talking about?
About the true power.
Sensei, will you get back to the course material?!
You have an interesting flower.
My dad brought it back from overseas.
Want to go eat pafe at "Basha Michi?"
Sheesh!  Not now...
Foreign flower?  That's interesting!
Matsunaga!
There are certain things she can't wait, I guess.
This must be...
Leave me alone!
What are you doing in front of the girls' restroom?
I wanted to ask a student in there about paranormal phenomena.
What kind of paranormal phenomena exist in girls' restrooms?
What is it?
Kageura was asking me about the bracelet.
Let's take it off for a while.
Kageura is really pesky.
And I have his class everyday.
That's bad enough.
I really like this flower though.
Me too.  After all, it syncs with our wavelengths.
Why did you turn off the TV?
Tonight's dish looks very delicious.
Thanks for the food!
Don't forget the prayer.
Heavenly light stone?
I am Keitaro Asou.
The Heavenly light stone stimulate the hidden human power.
I am convinced that there is a deposit of the mineral in Mount Kongo.
Lets eat now...
I'm not familier with the stone.
If it's discovered, it could greatly enhance the development of ESP.
Its very rude to stand up during a meal!
Ah?  I'm sorry.
Juliet, I'm going to find the heavenly light stone deposit!
All it takes is to build a sensor to detect the alpha waves emitted by the stone!
I'm... blah blah
Juliet...
How many times do I have to tell you to not touch this water?
Juliet, did you bring this for my research fund?
What a nice raven you are!
Juliet, next time, bring me paper money!
I-Is it possible... that I have created a life?!
Oh Lord.  Forgive me for my talent and intelligence!
More!   More!
More!   Oh Lord!
Huh?!
What just happened?
The voodoo mask?
EH?!  Whats this?!
Th-This...
I see!   I have acquired ESP!
Now!  Where could it be?
Found a 100 yen coin!
No need for a machine anymore.  I can find the deposit once I get there.
There's a 500 yen coin!
Blow harder wind!  Ah!  That's a 10 yen coin!
Generally when solid liquid or gas coexist with other phases, one of the phase will exist as minute particles.
Textbooks are like a bible for students, you shouldn't abuse it.
Collided particles are one micron to hundred micron big.  They are bigger than atoms and ions.
Sensei, are you going to teach chemistry today?!
You ask strange questions.  I am a chemistry teacher, why shouldn't I?
Ah...
Hey!  My fellow super people.
"Fellow"?
"Super people"?
Now I see why you two tried so hard to hide your powers.  This power is indeed not something to be shown to others.
You two look surprised.  I'm telling you, that I now have the same power as you two.
Same powers?
Mine may be stronger than yours.
Honjitsu TV?
I would like to get in contact with Keitaro Asou, who was on last night's "Hidden Secrets of the Heavenly Light Stone".
That's right.  There is something I want to talk to him about, with the relation between the stone and ESP powers.
It wasn't a trick was it?
He was definitely floating and there was no devices around him.
Hard to believe it though.
Yeah...
Shin-chan, dinner time!
Yes!
Say...
I think this flower looks weak.
I hope this will do.
Get well soon.
Listen Lica-chan.
What is it?
There is something I want to tell you about.
What could that be?
It's something that I myself find hard to believe...
I can't believe there's things you can't believe.
I've never imagined this would happen to me.
You mean?!
That's right.  I've become an ESPer.
That's all?!
I was wondering what you were going to say, but I'm relieved now!
Come on!
Do you really understand this...?
Thus, Satsuma and Choshu united the force by the work of a ronin called Ryoma Sakamoto.
And this was the dawn of the modern nation...
Sensei!
May I be excused?  I have a sick friend.
I'll hand in a permit form tomorrow. Excuse me!
Mikage!
What, you're leaving too?
Mikage, did you hear that?
Yes, the flowers were crying.
Is it dead?
No, its not!
But its color has changed.
Will you shutup?  That's why I'm looking into it right now.
But you...
But you know...?
Speak to us...  What can we do for you?
Oh stop it, Shin-chan!
Ya!  More Shin-chan, do more!
More!  More!
Ya, Good morning!
Good morning, Shin-chan.
Now, let's warm up.  1 2 3 heeve!
I should be in good shape...
This can't be... MOVE!
Move...!   MOOVE!!
It moved!
My god... for a moment, I thought I lost the power.  Thank heavens!
Wait a minute, can't we rest?!
Again?  If we don't hurry,
we'll be caught in the rain.
It's alright!
Once I get into the mountain, I'll find it right away.
That's the mountain.
Lets see.  This is the tree,
I found the ore right here!
What?  Thats strange...
Did you find it?!
Kageura!
We're being pulled in!
The heavenly light stone is right here!
I'm flying thru the air!
Thats Kageura...!
What's going on?!
Eh?!  What?!  Climb up!  Climb!
I feel heavy...
Weird...
It's this stone, I bet.
Yea, the flowers are healthy again!  Right?
Yes.
Did this stone draw us here?
Kageura-san, wake up!
Therefore, the healing method whereby the hand contacts with the affected part to provide a cure is seen throughout the world.
You have a very nice pendant.
What are you talking about?
Tomomi, help!
Hold it, Matsunaga!
Let me see that pendant!
Catch!  It's yours!
Stop!
In our next episode...
I feel so drowsy.
Hang in there!
If we don't have enough sleep, we can see future visions.
Really?
So, lets stay up.
Next on Miracle Girls: "Precognition Index? Percent"
Mikage, can we predict what's on the exam, too?
Whatever we do,
there has to be both of us.
Even if we had a fight,
There are days when kindness is so close that you can't see it.
Even if we know better than anyone else.
Subtitled by Studio Hooseki.
www.miwasoft.com/hooseki
When we can't say "I'm sorry,"
Subtitled by Studio Hooseki.
www.miwasoft.com/hooseki
we send out feelings through the little fingers.
Going over the tears,
we want to be honest to ourselves.
'Cause the sky deserves a rainbow.
Whatever we do,
there has to be both of us.
Subtitled by Studio Hooseki.
www.miwasoft.com/hooseki