Halfway through a kiss,
Miracle Girls
tears dropped out.
Original Work by Nanami Akimoto
(Serialized in "Nakayoshi")
Character Design:
Yoshihisa Sekine
Series Coordinator:
Hirokazu Kobayashi
Because I closed my heart
Filming Director:
Hieao Shirai
Art Director:
Takashi Nakamura
and distanced myself from you.
5 PM in the school yard.
Music:
Michiru Oshima
Filming Director:
Hieoao Shirai
The ball's shadow is growing tall.
Opening Song
"Halfway Through a Kiss, Tears"
("Kiss no Tochu de Namida ga")
by GARDEN
Don't be so quiet.
Ending Song
"There has to be Both of Us"
("Futarijanakya Dame Nano")
By Dio
Whenever we meet in the hallway,
we always quarreled.
Halfway through a kiss,
Producers:
Shinichiro Maeda,
Yuhko Sasagawa
& Ken Yorita
tears dropped out.
Director:
Takashi Anno
Because I opened my heart
Created by
Nihon TV
and we understand each other.
Produced by
Japan Taps & ASATSU
Translation by
Naoki Mizutani
Episode 19
Voice Calling
into Fog
Good morning, Tirano.
Morning, Tomomi-chan.
Today, I'm a year older than you. Morning, Trikela.
Morning, Ryoko-chan. Morning, Sakko-chan, Mikage-chan.
Bye!
Aren't you going anywhere?
I can't go to date.
'Cause your date is in London?
I wish I could go there again.
But you've never been there. If you're leaving, make sure to lock the door.
See you.
Tomomi-chan.
Yamagishi-kun.
Hi, what're you doing here?
Well.. you see..
I never thought I'd run into you here. What do you say?
I was thinking of going over to the dinosaur exhibition.
Dinosaur Exhibition?
Wanna go? Come on, let's go.
Noda-kun.
What're you doing here?
Noda? Good thing you're around too. I'll take you along too.
Take me along?
To a dinosaur exhibition.
Dinosaur?
Aren't you two lucky to get to see dinosaurs with my commentaries?
Let's go.
But we're...
Now that all three of us bumped into each other, why not?
Tomomi and I didn't bump in.
Are you two.. I see.
That's right.
You got it. OK?
I see. So you two were planning to go with me from the beginning.
Yamagishi, you've got something wrong...
Noda, what a good guy you are, not that your face is.
You're embarrassing me.
But I'll take your generosity. Let's go enjoy ourselves.
Yamagishi, listen...
Let's get going. It'll get crowded.
Oy, Yamagishi!
What?
I can't do that.
Why not? This fossil has quite clear shape.
It'll make very good study material for my students.
But that doesn't mean I can give away a paving stone.
That's why I'm asking you.
No matter how much you ask, no.
Ammonite?
Younger Matsunaga? Glad to see you.
Tell him how rare fossil like this is...
Can't believe there's a fossil here.
There's lots of precious fossils like this all over this town.
If there's, why don't you go somewhere else?
I tried everywhere else with no luck! That's why I'm begging you!
Knock it off. I can't believe this man...
What do you mean? Younger Matsunaga, tell him.
At any rate, I can't let go of this paving stone!
Sensei, are there other fossils like this one?
Tons of them. The buildings around here are quite old.
- There're numerous ancient romance all over...
- Thank you, sensei.
Hey, Matsunaga, I already asked for other fossils.
Awesome.
Really, they are.
That's stegosaurus.
So, animals like these were roaming all over in ancient times.
Do you know why the dinosaurs became extinct?
'Cause ice age began?
No, it was because of massive tectonic activity.
Neither. The most popular theory now is a meteor.
Meteor?
A huge meteor struck Earth, and dust from the impact covered the entire Earth.
That's why the temperature went down.
How can you be so sure?
It's more interesting that way.
They couldn't adopt to the change in environment.
I'm surprised.
You know so much about dinosaurs.
Wanna date with me?
You dummy.
Look at this. There was a bird like this?
What's wrong? Are you OK?
I must've seen the memory of the fossil.
Sorry. I'm OK now.
Fossil's memory?
There's no limit to your power, is there?
Scared?
Of course not. Will get mad if I tell ya, that's interesting?
What are they whispering about? Dammit... today's my...
No way!
What's the...
What was that?
Must be trick of our eyes.
Gotta be. Or else, everybody else would have been in panic, too.
It could be my fault.
So what did you think about it?
Great. We saw something weird, but that's interesting too.
Say, wanna play "it" for height?
Sure.
Wait up, Tomomi-chan!
About that dinosaur...
The one that hatched from the egg?
Was that you?
Are you alright?
Yeah. I'm OK. I don't know.
I did draw that out of fossil, so it could be.
But I didn't even touch the egg. So I really don't know.
You don't know the limit of your power. Just about the same as me.
In the summer game preliminary, do you think I can win?
Yes way! Yu will for sure. You don't have limit either.
Hey, it's not hide and seek, is it?
Noda, stop joking and come out!
Is that...
What's wrong, Yamagishi?
Yamagishi-kun.
It's around here. There it is.
So I can find fossils in town too.
What's that?
What's the hell is that?
Apatosaurus. It used to be called brontosaurus.
One of the most popular herbivorous specie!
And what's it doing here?!
You tell me!
Are we the only ones who can see it?
It's more like Yamagishi-kun's the only one.
His excitement is flowing into us. I can feel that.
Is that a type of telepathy?
Don't know.
Let's ask him.
Why it appeared? Let's go ask him.
Ask him? You can't talk to him, can you?
I think telepathy would work.
What're you guys standing there for? Come on, move it!
I'll leave you behind!
Why do you have to tell me what to do? Besides today's...
Noda-kun, let's go. Now that I heard his voice, I can't leave him like that.
Wait up, Tomomi!
There might be around here too.
It's so strange...
An amber? It's so pretty. Can I have this?
Thank you. Naah, I've been selfish...
Pretty, isn't it? It's like a treasure.
Hello. Do you want this? You can have it.
It's OK. I know even a better one.
A better one?
Yeah.
Sorry.
I'm really sorry.
He turned this way.
Wow, what a tunnel.
There.
Awesome, isn't it?
It really is...
He must be looking for others. Humans aren't one of his kind.
Probably. After all, dinosaurs died out before humans were around.
The dinosaurs lived in the same time as humans.
Same time?
There're lots of drawing of dinosaurs.
There's even ancient dolls that look like nothing but dinosaurs.
If they died out before our time, how come early humans could make those things?
It's your treasure, isn't it?
It's my secret. Keep it secret.
Sure. Let me swear for it.
"We'll swear or we'll swallow thousand needles."
Bye-bye!
Bye.
No way...
It disappeared.
Yamagishi, you really know about dinosaurs, don't ya?
Impressed?
Just a bit.
He must be lonely. He's gotta be looking for others.
Tomomi, I just saw translucent dinosaur over there.
Yes, I know.
You too, Noda?
Yamagishi-kun noticed first.
What's that?
Pretty, isn't it? I bet it's a fern from the same time as him.
Then, he'd be very happy if we give him that.
After all, today's his birthday.
Birthday? Yamagishi, is your...
Let's go!
Again?
He must be heading for the ship.
Ship?
The ship's horn must sound like others that he's never seen.
Let's go.
He's leaving?
He's going home.
He must've never noticed us.
I wish I could say bye to him.
Me too.
Yamagishi, sorry.
About what?
About today.
What's the...
It's them. Move it, Yamagishi.
Hey, Noda!
This way!
What about Tomomi-chan and Mikage-chan?
They're probably in there.
Bye!
Good bye! Good bye!
I knew it.
Tomomi-tachi, how did you get up here?
Yamagishi-kun, look. The dinosaur turned this way.
Good bye.
The foghorn of the light house. Was that you two?
You know?
Are you sure?
It's pretty positive.
What's holding you?
Happy birthday!
Thank you.
Here's something for you.
Really? Thank you. Wow, it's a fern leaves.
When I wanna remember about the dinosaur, I'll look at this fossil.
Lemme see it once in awhile, will you?
Me too.
Sure, you two are welcome to see it anytime.
What about me?
Wanna see it?
Hey, that's no fair.
Miracle Girls here.
Typhoon's coming. I feel I can do anything now.
I'm gonna show off psychic power to Kageura.
I wanna check Noda-kun's feeling to me.
Next on Miracle Girls:
"Hurricane in Maiden's Heart"
Everything's going to start all over again in typhoon.
Whatever we do,
there has to be both of us.
Even if we had a fight,
There has to be both of us.
Ending Song
"There has to be Both of Us"
("Futarijanakya Dame Nano")
By Dio
There are days when kindness is so close
that you can't see it.
Even if we know it better than anyone else.
When we can't say "I'm sorry,"
we send out feelings through the little fingers.
Going over the tears,
we want to be honest to ourselves.
'Cause the sky deserves a rainbow.
Whatever we do,
there has to be both of us.
Two of us
are better than one of us.